1-GRAM  28339   O O
1-GRAM  9459    I-ORG I-NP
1-GRAM  26322   O I-VP
1-GRAM  4349    I-MISC I-NP
1-GRAM  87504   O I-NP
1-GRAM  10866   I-PER I-NP
1-GRAM  8008    I-LOC I-NP
1-GRAM  18478   O I-PP
1-GRAM  3474    O B-NP
1-GRAM  1277    O I-SBAR
1-GRAM  1327    O I-ADJP
1-GRAM  2701    O I-ADVP
1-GRAM  87      I-ORG B-NP
1-GRAM  38      I-MISC I-VP
1-GRAM  64      I-MISC O
1-GRAM  131     I-PER B-NP
1-GRAM  515     O I-PRT
1-GRAM  106     I-LOC I-VP
1-GRAM  163     O B-VP
1-GRAM  32      I-LOC B-NP
1-GRAM  145     I-ORG I-PP
1-GRAM  254     O B-PP
1-GRAM  56      I-PER I-VP
1-GRAM  5       I-LOC I-ADJP
1-GRAM  179     I-ORG I-VP
1-GRAM  70      O I-CONJP
1-GRAM  9       B-LOC I-NP
1-GRAM  53      I-MISC B-NP
1-GRAM  36      B-MISC I-NP
1-GRAM  7       I-LOC I-INTJ
1-GRAM  28      I-LOC I-PP
1-GRAM  32      O I-INTJ
1-GRAM  35      I-MISC I-PP
1-GRAM  18      I-PER I-ADJP
1-GRAM  16      I-ORG I-INTJ
1-GRAM  36      O I-LST
1-GRAM  23      I-PER I-ADVP
1-GRAM  11      I-MISC I-PRT
1-GRAM  5       I-PER I-PP
1-GRAM  79      I-LOC O
1-GRAM  23      I-PER O
1-GRAM  8       I-ORG I-ADVP
1-GRAM  22      O B-ADVP
1-GRAM  21      I-LOC I-ADVP
1-GRAM  86      I-ORG O
1-GRAM  6       I-MISC I-ADJP
1-GRAM  5       I-PER I-INTJ
1-GRAM  8       O B-SBAR
1-GRAM  18      I-ORG I-ADJP
1-GRAM  2       O B-ADJP
1-GRAM  3       I-ORG I-SBAR
1-GRAM  1       B-LOC I-PP
1-GRAM  1       B-LOC O
1-GRAM  24      B-ORG I-NP
1-GRAM  1       B-MISC I-VP
1-GRAM  1       I-PER I-PRT
2-GRAM  15063   O I-NP O O
2-GRAM  1288    O O I-ORG I-NP
2-GRAM  861     I-ORG I-NP O I-VP
2-GRAM  221     O I-VP I-MISC I-NP
2-GRAM  2259    I-MISC I-NP O I-NP
2-GRAM  9198    O I-NP O I-VP
2-GRAM  8680    O I-VP O I-VP
2-GRAM  3070    O I-NP I-PER I-NP
2-GRAM  4387    I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP
2-GRAM  73      I-PER I-NP I-LOC I-NP
2-GRAM  1967    I-LOC I-NP O I-NP
2-GRAM  43699   O I-NP O I-NP
2-GRAM  3629    O I-NP I-ORG I-NP
2-GRAM  3206    I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP
2-GRAM  3874    O I-VP O I-PP
2-GRAM  14090   O I-PP O I-NP
2-GRAM  2337    O I-NP O B-NP
2-GRAM  753     O B-NP O I-VP
2-GRAM  495     O I-PP I-MISC I-NP
2-GRAM  11153   O I-NP O I-PP
2-GRAM  545     O I-NP O I-SBAR
2-GRAM  948     O I-SBAR O I-NP
2-GRAM  323     O I-VP O I-SBAR
2-GRAM  2261    O I-NP I-LOC I-NP
2-GRAM  494     I-LOC I-NP O B-NP
2-GRAM  2152    O B-NP O I-NP
2-GRAM  269     I-ORG I-NP O B-NP
2-GRAM  1511    I-PER I-NP O I-VP
2-GRAM  8096    O I-VP O I-NP
2-GRAM  261     O I-NP O I-ADJP
2-GRAM  357     O I-ADJP O I-PP
2-GRAM  1835    O I-PP I-LOC I-NP
2-GRAM  34      I-LOC I-NP O I-SBAR
2-GRAM  658     O I-VP O I-ADJP
2-GRAM  328     O I-ADJP O O
2-GRAM  8162    O O O I-NP
2-GRAM  2123    O O O O
2-GRAM  1938    O I-VP O O
2-GRAM  182     O O O I-SBAR
2-GRAM  1212    I-ORG I-NP O O
2-GRAM  433     O I-PP I-ORG I-NP
2-GRAM  3306    I-ORG I-NP O I-NP
2-GRAM  208     O I-ADJP O I-ADJP
2-GRAM  148     O I-ADJP O I-NP
2-GRAM  1026    I-PER I-NP O I-NP
2-GRAM  1895    O I-NP I-MISC I-NP
2-GRAM  212     I-MISC I-NP O I-VP
2-GRAM  55      O B-NP O I-PP
2-GRAM  985     I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP
2-GRAM  405     I-MISC I-NP O O
2-GRAM  477     O O I-MISC I-NP
2-GRAM  1968    O O I-PER I-NP
2-GRAM  2925    O O O I-VP
2-GRAM  58      O I-PP O I-ADVP
2-GRAM  469     O I-ADVP O I-VP
2-GRAM  713     O I-VP O I-ADVP
2-GRAM  718     O I-ADVP O I-NP
2-GRAM  600     O I-VP I-PER I-NP
2-GRAM  382     I-PER I-NP O I-PP
2-GRAM  613     O I-PP O I-VP
2-GRAM  152     O I-PP O O
2-GRAM  614     I-LOC I-NP O I-VP
2-GRAM  286     I-PER I-NP O B-NP
2-GRAM  202     O I-ADJP O I-VP
2-GRAM  49      I-MISC I-NP O B-NP
2-GRAM  31      O I-SBAR I-MISC I-NP
2-GRAM  3004    I-LOC I-NP O O
2-GRAM  298     O I-VP I-LOC I-NP
2-GRAM  49      I-ORG I-NP I-ORG B-NP
2-GRAM  30      I-ORG B-NP I-ORG I-NP
2-GRAM  837     O O O I-PP
2-GRAM  23      O O I-MISC I-VP
2-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-VP I-MISC O
2-GRAM  7       I-MISC O I-MISC I-NP
2-GRAM  11      I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-VP
2-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-VP O O
2-GRAM  120     O I-NP I-PER B-NP
2-GRAM  14      I-PER B-NP O I-VP
2-GRAM  466     O O O I-ADVP
2-GRAM  1077    O I-NP O I-ADVP
2-GRAM  464     O I-VP O I-PRT
2-GRAM  147     O I-PRT O I-PP
2-GRAM  395     O I-PP I-PER I-NP
2-GRAM  3088    I-PER I-NP O O
2-GRAM  2259    O O I-LOC I-NP
2-GRAM  76      O I-NP I-LOC I-VP
2-GRAM  85      I-LOC I-VP O I-NP
2-GRAM  538     I-LOC I-NP O I-PP
2-GRAM  1098    I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP
2-GRAM  280     O I-VP I-ORG I-NP
2-GRAM  158     O I-VP O B-VP
2-GRAM  111     O B-VP O I-VP
2-GRAM  123     O B-NP I-ORG I-NP
2-GRAM  257     I-ORG I-NP O I-PP
2-GRAM  592     O I-ADVP O I-PP
2-GRAM  27      O I-NP I-LOC B-NP
2-GRAM  14      I-LOC B-NP O I-VP
2-GRAM  128     I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-PP
2-GRAM  138     I-ORG I-PP I-ORG I-NP
2-GRAM  561     O I-ADVP O O
2-GRAM  43      I-ORG I-NP O I-ADVP
2-GRAM  251     O I-PP O B-PP
2-GRAM  211     O B-PP O I-NP
2-GRAM  25      O I-NP I-PER I-VP
2-GRAM  20      I-PER I-VP I-PER I-NP
2-GRAM  102     I-PER B-NP I-PER I-NP
2-GRAM  2       O O I-LOC I-ADJP
2-GRAM  2       I-LOC I-ADJP O I-NP
2-GRAM  113     O I-NP I-ORG I-VP
2-GRAM  16      I-ORG I-VP I-ORG I-NP
2-GRAM  65      I-LOC I-NP O I-ADVP
2-GRAM  206     O I-PRT O I-NP
2-GRAM  2       O I-VP O I-CONJP
2-GRAM  39      O I-CONJP O I-CONJP
2-GRAM  18      O I-CONJP O I-NP
2-GRAM  85      O B-NP I-MISC I-NP
2-GRAM  49      O I-SBAR I-LOC I-NP
2-GRAM  9       I-LOC I-NP B-LOC I-NP
2-GRAM  1       B-LOC I-NP O I-VP
2-GRAM  15      O B-PP I-LOC I-NP
2-GRAM  46      O I-ADJP O I-SBAR
2-GRAM  74      O I-SBAR I-PER I-NP
2-GRAM  107     O O O I-ADJP
2-GRAM  100     O I-PP O I-PP
2-GRAM  86      I-MISC I-NP I-ORG I-NP
2-GRAM  126     I-MISC I-NP O I-PP
2-GRAM  46      I-PER I-NP O I-ADVP
2-GRAM  10      I-MISC I-NP I-LOC I-NP
2-GRAM  5       I-LOC B-NP O I-NP
2-GRAM  24      O I-ADVP I-LOC I-NP
2-GRAM  19      O I-NP I-MISC B-NP
2-GRAM  10      I-MISC B-NP O I-VP
2-GRAM  35      I-MISC I-NP B-MISC I-NP
2-GRAM  13      B-MISC I-NP O I-NP
2-GRAM  51      O I-SBAR O I-VP
2-GRAM  85      O B-NP I-PER I-NP
2-GRAM  15      I-PER I-NP O I-SBAR
2-GRAM  2       O I-PP I-LOC I-INTJ
2-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-INTJ I-LOC I-NP
2-GRAM  15      O I-NP I-LOC I-PP
2-GRAM  3       I-LOC I-PP O I-NP
2-GRAM  2       O B-VP O O
2-GRAM  6       O I-NP O I-INTJ
2-GRAM  1       O I-INTJ O I-PP
2-GRAM  25      O I-SBAR O I-PP
2-GRAM  104     O B-NP O O
2-GRAM  10      I-ORG I-NP I-MISC I-NP
2-GRAM  7       O O O I-INTJ
2-GRAM  3       O I-INTJ O I-NP
2-GRAM  35      O B-NP O B-NP
2-GRAM  134     O I-ADVP O I-ADVP
2-GRAM  27      O I-PP O I-ADJP
2-GRAM  11      O I-SBAR O I-ADVP
2-GRAM  34      I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-PP
2-GRAM  35      I-MISC I-PP I-MISC I-NP
2-GRAM  4       I-LOC B-NP O I-SBAR
2-GRAM  6       I-ORG I-NP O I-INTJ
2-GRAM  32      I-MISC I-NP I-MISC B-NP
2-GRAM  7       I-MISC I-VP I-MISC I-NP
2-GRAM  13      O I-NP I-PER I-ADJP
2-GRAM  14      I-PER I-ADJP O O
2-GRAM  55      O I-ADVP O I-SBAR
2-GRAM  1       O I-PP I-PER I-VP
2-GRAM  17      O O I-PER I-VP
2-GRAM  9       I-ORG I-VP O I-VP
2-GRAM  6       O I-VP I-ORG I-VP
2-GRAM  2       I-ORG I-VP O I-PP
2-GRAM  19      I-MISC B-NP O I-NP
2-GRAM  20      B-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP
2-GRAM  95      O I-PRT O O
2-GRAM  35      O O I-ORG I-VP
2-GRAM  146     I-ORG I-VP O I-NP
2-GRAM  6       O O I-ORG I-INTJ
2-GRAM  5       I-ORG I-INTJ O O
2-GRAM  5       I-PER I-NP O I-LST
2-GRAM  12      O I-LST O O
2-GRAM  11      O I-NP I-PER I-ADVP
2-GRAM  4       I-PER I-ADVP I-PER I-NP
2-GRAM  35      O I-NP I-MISC O
2-GRAM  6       I-MISC O I-MISC I-PRT
2-GRAM  6       I-MISC I-PRT O O
2-GRAM  6       O I-ADVP O I-LST
2-GRAM  19      O I-LST O I-NP
2-GRAM  3       O I-NP I-PER I-PP
2-GRAM  4       I-PER I-PP I-PER I-NP
2-GRAM  37      O I-NP I-ORG B-NP
2-GRAM  11      I-ORG B-NP O I-VP
2-GRAM  5       I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-PRT
2-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-PRT I-MISC I-NP
2-GRAM  16      I-MISC B-NP I-MISC I-NP
2-GRAM  5       O I-NP O I-LST
2-GRAM  17      I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-VP
2-GRAM  3       I-ORG I-VP O O
2-GRAM  16      O O O I-LST
2-GRAM  1       O B-NP I-ORG B-NP
2-GRAM  32      I-ORG B-NP O I-NP
2-GRAM  10      O I-NP I-ORG I-INTJ
2-GRAM  6       I-ORG I-INTJ O I-NP
2-GRAM  13      I-PER I-VP O I-NP
2-GRAM  3       I-MISC I-PRT O I-NP
2-GRAM  20      I-MISC I-NP I-MISC O
2-GRAM  11      I-MISC O O I-NP
2-GRAM  25      I-MISC I-VP O I-NP
2-GRAM  1       I-PER I-NP I-MISC I-NP
2-GRAM  62      O O I-LOC O
2-GRAM  65      I-LOC O O O
2-GRAM  4       O I-NP I-PER O
2-GRAM  9       I-PER O O O
2-GRAM  2       I-PER I-VP I-PER O
2-GRAM  8       I-PER I-NP I-PER I-VP
2-GRAM  8       I-PER I-VP O O
2-GRAM  5       O I-ADJP I-PER I-NP
2-GRAM  41      O B-NP I-LOC I-NP
2-GRAM  96      I-LOC I-NP I-ORG I-NP
2-GRAM  6       I-LOC I-NP I-ORG I-VP
2-GRAM  7       I-LOC I-VP I-LOC I-NP
2-GRAM  38      I-LOC I-NP I-MISC I-NP
2-GRAM  49      O I-ADVP I-PER I-NP
2-GRAM  6       I-MISC I-NP O I-SBAR
2-GRAM  43      O I-NP O I-PRT
2-GRAM  27      O I-PRT O I-VP
2-GRAM  5       O I-PRT I-ORG I-NP
2-GRAM  4       O I-NP I-ORG I-ADVP
2-GRAM  8       I-ORG I-ADVP O I-NP
2-GRAM  7       O B-VP O I-PP
2-GRAM  13      O I-PRT O I-ADVP
2-GRAM  6       I-PER I-NP I-PER I-ADVP
2-GRAM  12      I-PER I-ADVP O O
2-GRAM  29      O B-NP O I-ADVP
2-GRAM  1       I-MISC O O I-VP
2-GRAM  4       O O I-ORG I-PP
2-GRAM  8       O I-NP I-ORG I-PP
2-GRAM  44      O I-ADVP O I-ADJP
2-GRAM  22      O I-ADVP O B-ADVP
2-GRAM  6       O B-ADVP O I-NP
2-GRAM  37      O I-SBAR I-ORG I-NP
2-GRAM  10      I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-PP
2-GRAM  11      I-LOC I-PP I-LOC I-NP
2-GRAM  4       O I-SBAR O I-ADJP
2-GRAM  5       O B-VP O I-ADVP
2-GRAM  26      O B-VP O I-NP
2-GRAM  6       O I-PRT I-PER I-NP
2-GRAM  59      I-MISC I-NP I-PER I-NP
2-GRAM  5       I-PER I-NP O I-ADJP
2-GRAM  21      O I-ADJP O I-ADVP
2-GRAM  19      O I-NP I-LOC I-ADVP
2-GRAM  17      I-LOC I-ADVP O I-NP
2-GRAM  34      I-MISC O O O
2-GRAM  6       O I-NP I-ORG O
2-GRAM  11      I-ORG O O O
2-GRAM  60      I-ORG I-NP I-ORG O
2-GRAM  48      I-ORG O I-ORG I-NP
2-GRAM  7       O B-PP I-PER I-NP
2-GRAM  4       O I-PRT I-MISC I-NP
2-GRAM  5       O I-NP I-LOC I-INTJ
2-GRAM  5       I-LOC I-INTJ O O
2-GRAM  18      O I-SBAR O O
2-GRAM  2       I-PER I-NP I-PER I-ADJP
2-GRAM  1       I-PER I-ADJP O I-VP
2-GRAM  7       O B-NP O I-SBAR
2-GRAM  14      I-ORG I-NP O I-SBAR
2-GRAM  19      O I-SBAR O I-SBAR
2-GRAM  7       I-ORG B-NP O O
2-GRAM  1       O I-ADVP O I-PRT
2-GRAM  4       O O I-MISC O
2-GRAM  8       O I-INTJ O O
2-GRAM  5       I-PER I-VP O I-VP
2-GRAM  2       I-PER I-NP I-PER I-PP
2-GRAM  2       I-ORG B-NP I-ORG I-PP
2-GRAM  3       O B-VP O I-ADJP
2-GRAM  14      I-LOC I-PP I-LOC I-VP
2-GRAM  6       O O I-LOC I-VP
2-GRAM  1       O O I-LOC I-PP
2-GRAM  13      O I-NP O I-CONJP
2-GRAM  3       O I-INTJ O I-VP
2-GRAM  11      O I-ADVP I-MISC I-NP
2-GRAM  3       I-MISC O I-MISC I-ADJP
2-GRAM  4       I-MISC I-ADJP O O
2-GRAM  3       O I-NP I-LOC I-ADJP
2-GRAM  3       I-LOC I-ADJP O O
2-GRAM  5       O O I-PER O
2-GRAM  3       I-PER O I-PER O
2-GRAM  1       I-PER I-ADVP O I-CONJP
2-GRAM  1       O I-CONJP O I-PRT
2-GRAM  6       O O I-PER I-ADVP
2-GRAM  3       I-PER I-ADVP O I-NP
2-GRAM  2       O B-ADVP O I-SBAR
2-GRAM  6       O B-PP I-MISC I-NP
2-GRAM  3       O I-ADJP I-MISC I-NP
2-GRAM  4       I-PER B-NP O I-NP
2-GRAM  1       I-PER B-NP I-PER O
2-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-PRT O I-VP
2-GRAM  9       I-LOC I-NP O I-INTJ
2-GRAM  6       I-LOC I-VP O O
2-GRAM  1       O I-ADJP I-ORG I-NP
2-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-NP I-PER B-NP
2-GRAM  6       O I-PRT O I-SBAR
2-GRAM  12      O I-PP O I-SBAR
2-GRAM  15      O I-ADVP I-ORG I-NP
2-GRAM  11      I-MISC I-NP O I-ADVP
2-GRAM  3       I-LOC I-NP O I-ADJP
2-GRAM  3       O B-PP O B-PP
2-GRAM  3       O I-NP I-PER I-INTJ
2-GRAM  3       I-PER I-INTJ O O
2-GRAM  7       I-ORG I-NP I-PER I-NP
2-GRAM  10      I-PER I-NP I-PER B-NP
2-GRAM  7       I-PER B-NP O O
2-GRAM  1       O I-PP I-MISC I-PP
2-GRAM  3       O B-ADVP O I-PP
2-GRAM  8       O I-SBAR O B-SBAR
2-GRAM  8       O B-SBAR O I-NP
2-GRAM  4       I-LOC I-ADVP O O
2-GRAM  4       O I-LST O I-LST
2-GRAM  3       O B-VP O I-SBAR
2-GRAM  3       I-ORG I-NP O I-CONJP
2-GRAM  1       I-PER I-NP I-LOC I-PP
2-GRAM  1       O I-ADJP O I-CONJP
2-GRAM  4       I-MISC B-NP O I-SBAR
2-GRAM  2       I-ORG B-NP O I-PP
2-GRAM  10      I-ORG O O I-NP
2-GRAM  2       I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-ADVP
2-GRAM  4       I-ORG O I-ORG O
2-GRAM  14      O I-NP I-ORG I-ADJP
2-GRAM  8       I-ORG I-ADJP O I-NP
2-GRAM  3       O O O I-PRT
2-GRAM  2       I-PER I-NP I-LOC I-VP
2-GRAM  1       I-PER I-ADVP O I-VP
2-GRAM  10      O O O I-CONJP
2-GRAM  4       O I-CONJP O I-PP
2-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-VP I-PER I-NP
2-GRAM  1       I-PER I-ADVP O I-ADVP
2-GRAM  3       O B-VP I-PER I-NP
2-GRAM  2       I-LOC I-VP O I-INTJ
2-GRAM  7       O I-INTJ I-LOC I-NP
2-GRAM  7       I-ORG I-PP O I-NP
2-GRAM  2       O O I-ORG I-ADVP
2-GRAM  1       O I-VP O I-INTJ
2-GRAM  6       O I-INTJ I-ORG I-NP
2-GRAM  3       I-ORG I-ADJP O O
2-GRAM  1       I-PER B-NP O B-NP
2-GRAM  2       I-PER B-NP O I-PP
2-GRAM  3       O B-PP O I-VP
2-GRAM  3       I-MISC I-NP O I-ADJP
2-GRAM  1       O B-VP O B-VP
2-GRAM  3       O I-PP I-MISC O
2-GRAM  1       I-PER I-ADVP I-LOC I-NP
2-GRAM  2       O B-PP O O
2-GRAM  1       O I-CONJP O I-ADVP
2-GRAM  2       O I-ADJP O B-ADJP
2-GRAM  1       O B-ADJP O O
2-GRAM  7       I-LOC I-NP I-LOC O
2-GRAM  4       I-LOC O I-LOC O
2-GRAM  4       I-LOC O I-LOC I-NP
2-GRAM  3       O B-ADVP O I-VP
2-GRAM  2       O I-CONJP O O
2-GRAM  4       I-LOC B-NP I-LOC I-NP
2-GRAM  1       O I-ADJP O I-PRT
2-GRAM  5       O I-VP I-PER I-VP
2-GRAM  8       I-LOC I-NP I-PER I-NP
2-GRAM  3       O I-PP I-MISC I-VP
2-GRAM  2       I-MISC I-VP O I-VP
2-GRAM  1       I-PER I-VP O I-ADVP
2-GRAM  1       O B-NP I-MISC O
2-GRAM  13      O O I-ORG O
2-GRAM  1       I-PER I-NP I-LOC I-ADVP
2-GRAM  4       O I-CONJP O I-VP
2-GRAM  3       O I-NP I-ORG I-SBAR
2-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-SBAR O I-VP
2-GRAM  2       O I-ADJP I-LOC I-NP
2-GRAM  7       O B-PP I-ORG I-NP
2-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-NP I-LOC B-NP
2-GRAM  3       I-LOC B-NP O O
2-GRAM  1       O I-PP I-LOC O
2-GRAM  1       O I-CONJP O I-ADJP
2-GRAM  4       I-ORG O O I-VP
2-GRAM  3       I-MISC B-NP O O
2-GRAM  4       O B-ADVP O I-ADVP
2-GRAM  1       O I-PP I-ORG I-PP
2-GRAM  3       O I-NP I-LOC O
2-GRAM  1       I-LOC O O I-NP
2-GRAM  4       I-PER I-VP O I-PP
2-GRAM  1       B-MISC I-NP O I-PP
2-GRAM  2       O O I-PER I-ADJP
2-GRAM  4       O I-PRT I-LOC I-NP
2-GRAM  2       O I-PRT O I-ADJP
2-GRAM  1       O I-INTJ I-LOC I-VP
2-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-VP I-LOC I-VP
2-GRAM  3       I-LOC I-VP O I-PP
2-GRAM  7       I-PER I-NP I-PER O
2-GRAM  1       O I-PP I-ORG I-VP
2-GRAM  3       O B-ADVP O O
2-GRAM  2       I-ORG I-SBAR I-ORG I-NP
2-GRAM  2       I-ORG B-NP O B-NP
2-GRAM  1       I-PER I-PP O O
2-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-ADVP
2-GRAM  3       I-PER I-VP O B-VP
2-GRAM  2       I-MISC I-VP O I-PP
2-GRAM  4       I-ORG I-INTJ I-ORG I-NP
2-GRAM  3       I-PER O O I-VP
2-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-VP
2-GRAM  1       O B-NP O I-PRT
2-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP B-LOC I-PP
2-GRAM  1       B-LOC I-PP O I-NP
2-GRAM  7       B-LOC I-NP O I-NP
2-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP B-LOC O
2-GRAM  1       B-LOC O O I-NP
2-GRAM  3       I-LOC I-NP I-LOC B-NP
2-GRAM  1       I-PER I-ADJP I-PER I-NP
2-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-INTJ O I-NP
2-GRAM  1       I-ORG O I-ORG I-ADJP
2-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-ADJP I-ORG O
2-GRAM  1       I-LOC B-NP O I-ADVP
2-GRAM  2       O I-ADJP I-MISC I-ADJP
2-GRAM  2       I-MISC I-ADJP O I-NP
2-GRAM  6       I-ORG I-NP B-ORG I-NP
2-GRAM  18      B-ORG I-NP B-ORG I-NP
2-GRAM  5       B-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP
2-GRAM  1       B-ORG I-NP O I-NP
2-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-VP O B-VP
2-GRAM  3       O I-PP I-LOC I-VP
2-GRAM  2       B-MISC I-NP I-MISC B-NP
2-GRAM  1       I-PER I-ADJP O I-PP
2-GRAM  1       O I-NP B-MISC I-NP
2-GRAM  7       I-PER O I-PER I-NP
2-GRAM  1       I-PER O O I-NP
2-GRAM  1       O O I-ORG I-ADJP
2-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP O I-CONJP
2-GRAM  2       I-ORG I-NP I-LOC I-NP
2-GRAM  1       I-MISC B-NP I-PER I-NP
2-GRAM  2       O O I-PER I-INTJ
2-GRAM  2       I-PER I-INTJ I-PER I-NP
2-GRAM  1       O I-SBAR I-PER I-ADJP
2-GRAM  1       I-LOC B-NP O B-NP
2-GRAM  1       O I-PP I-LOC I-PP
2-GRAM  1       O I-INTJ O I-INTJ
2-GRAM  1       B-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP
2-GRAM  2       I-PER I-NP I-ORG I-NP
2-GRAM  1       O O I-MISC I-ADJP
2-GRAM  1       O I-LST I-PER I-NP
2-GRAM  1       O I-SBAR B-MISC I-VP
2-GRAM  1       B-MISC I-VP I-MISC I-NP
2-GRAM  2       O I-VP I-LOC I-VP
2-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-INTJ I-ORG O
2-GRAM  2       I-ORG I-ADJP O I-VP
2-GRAM  1       O B-VP I-ORG I-NP
2-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-ADJP I-ORG I-ADJP
2-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-ADJP I-ORG I-NP
2-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-VP I-ORG I-PP
2-GRAM  1       O B-NP O I-ADJP
2-GRAM  2       O I-INTJ I-LOC O
2-GRAM  1       I-LOC O O I-PP
2-GRAM  1       O B-ADVP I-LOC I-NP
2-GRAM  1       I-ORG B-NP O I-ADVP
2-GRAM  1       O I-VP I-PER I-PRT
2-GRAM  1       I-PER I-PRT O O
2-GRAM  2       I-ORG I-ADJP O I-PP
2-GRAM  1       O I-VP I-ORG I-ADJP
2-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-VP O I-VP
2-GRAM  1       O I-VP I-PER O
2-GRAM  1       O B-VP O I-PRT
2-GRAM  1       I-ORG O I-ORG I-PP
2-GRAM  1       I-ORG O I-ORG I-VP
2-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-VP I-ORG O
2-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-MISC I-VP
2-GRAM  1       O B-ADJP O I-VP
2-GRAM  1       O B-NP I-LOC B-NP
2-GRAM  1       I-PER I-ADJP O I-NP
3-GRAM  9404    O I-NP O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  600     O I-NP O O I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  102     O O I-ORG I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  10      I-ORG I-NP O I-VP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  137     O I-VP I-MISC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  397     I-MISC I-NP O I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  3551    O I-NP O I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  61      O I-VP O I-VP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  400     I-MISC I-NP O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  2088    O I-NP O I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  2246    O I-NP I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  69      I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  42      I-PER I-NP I-LOC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  819     I-LOC I-NP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1793    O I-NP O I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1515    O I-NP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  398     I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  123     I-ORG I-NP O I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  3093    O I-VP O I-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  394     O I-PP O I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  671     O I-NP O B-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  91      O B-NP O I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  86      O I-VP O I-PP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  308     O I-PP I-MISC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  302     I-MISC I-NP O I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  8412    O I-NP O I-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  472     O I-PP O I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  25      I-MISC I-NP O I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  415     O I-NP O I-SBAR O I-NP
3-GRAM  419     O I-SBAR O I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  122     O I-NP O I-VP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  217     O I-VP O I-SBAR O I-NP
3-GRAM  347     O I-SBAR O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  20908   O I-NP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  4598    O I-NP O I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  2806    O I-VP O I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  1601    O I-VP O I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1926    O I-PP O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  1234    O I-NP O I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  113     O I-NP I-LOC I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  334     I-LOC I-NP O B-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  316     O B-NP O I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  377     O I-PP O I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  58      I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  196     I-ORG I-NP O B-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  900     O B-NP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  613     I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  168     I-PER I-NP O I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  8309    O I-PP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2680    O I-VP O I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  960     O I-VP O I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  19      O I-PP O I-NP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  91      O I-NP O I-ADJP O I-PP
3-GRAM  21      O I-ADJP O I-PP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  19      O I-PP I-LOC I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  24      I-LOC I-NP O I-SBAR O I-NP
3-GRAM  332     O I-NP O I-VP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  144     O I-VP O I-ADJP O O
3-GRAM  4475    O I-NP O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  1744    O O O I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  5132    O I-VP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  315     O I-NP O I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  7467    O I-NP O I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1256    O I-NP O O O O
3-GRAM  835     O O O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  199     O O O I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  75      O I-NP I-ORG I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  230     I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  576     I-PER I-NP O I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2429    O I-NP O I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  491     O I-VP O I-VP O O
3-GRAM  20      O I-VP O O O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  134     O O O I-SBAR O I-NP
3-GRAM  95      O I-VP O I-VP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  658     O I-VP O I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  554     I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP O O
3-GRAM  1375    O I-NP O I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  1340    O I-NP O B-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  319     O I-NP O I-PP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  67      O I-PP I-ORG I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1404    I-ORG I-NP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  346     I-PER I-NP O I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  1216    O O O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  3785    O O O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  167     O I-NP O I-NP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  33      O I-NP O I-ADJP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  24      O I-ADJP O I-ADJP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  30      O I-ADJP O I-ADJP O I-NP
3-GRAM  26      O I-ADJP O I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  171     O I-NP I-PER I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  8       I-PER I-NP O I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  87      O I-NP I-MISC I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  38      I-MISC I-NP O I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1261    O I-PP O I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1170    O I-NP O I-PP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  194     O I-PP I-LOC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  264     I-LOC I-NP O I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  3       I-LOC I-NP O B-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  39      O B-NP O I-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  273     O B-NP O I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  31      O I-VP I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  220     I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  156     I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  26      I-MISC I-NP O O I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  36      O O I-MISC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  48      I-MISC I-NP O O O O
3-GRAM  885     O I-NP O O I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  354     O O I-PER I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  1521    O I-NP O O O I-VP
3-GRAM  44      O O O I-VP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  12      O I-VP O I-PP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  9       O I-PP O I-ADVP O I-VP
3-GRAM  15      O I-ADVP O I-VP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  168     O I-VP O I-ADVP O I-NP
3-GRAM  341     O I-ADVP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  650     O I-NP O I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1103    O I-NP I-MISC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  818     I-MISC I-NP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  79      O I-VP O I-VP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  55      O I-VP I-PER I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  251     I-PER I-NP O I-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1413    O I-NP I-ORG I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  363     O I-NP O I-PP O I-VP
3-GRAM  2       O I-PP O I-VP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  49      O I-VP O I-ADJP O I-NP
3-GRAM  17      O I-ADJP O I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  104     O I-NP O I-PP O O
3-GRAM  58      O I-PP O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  988     O I-NP I-LOC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  180     O I-NP I-LOC I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  7       I-LOC I-NP O I-VP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  45      O I-VP I-PER I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  243     I-PER I-NP O B-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  428     O B-NP O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  131     O I-VP O I-ADJP O I-VP
3-GRAM  178     O I-ADJP O I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  1000    O O O I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O I-ADJP O I-PP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O I-PP I-MISC I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  18      I-MISC I-NP O B-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  335     O B-NP O I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  1239    O I-NP O I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  213     O B-NP O I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  287     O O O O O I-VP
3-GRAM  49      O I-VP O I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  16      O I-NP O I-SBAR I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  18      O I-SBAR I-MISC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  702     O I-PP I-LOC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  118     O O O I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  182     O I-VP O I-VP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  129     O I-VP O I-ADJP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  55      O I-ADJP O I-ADJP O I-PP
3-GRAM  23      O I-ADJP O I-PP O I-VP
3-GRAM  15      O I-PP O I-VP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  105     O I-VP O I-VP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  54      O I-VP I-LOC I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  105     O O O O I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  433     O O I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  815     I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  9       I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG B-NP
3-GRAM  19      I-ORG I-NP I-ORG B-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  4       I-ORG B-NP I-ORG I-NP O O
3-GRAM  212     I-ORG I-NP O O I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  242     O O I-ORG I-NP O O
3-GRAM  264     I-ORG I-NP O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  194     O O O I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  69      O I-VP O I-PP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  168     O I-PP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  250     I-LOC I-NP O I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  613     O I-PP O I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  65      O I-ADJP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  72      O I-PP O I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  539     O I-VP O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  185     I-LOC I-NP O I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  194     O I-PP I-LOC I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  363     O I-NP O I-PP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  325     I-PER I-NP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  139     I-LOC I-NP O I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  498     O I-NP O O O I-PP
3-GRAM  594     O O O I-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PP O O I-MISC I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O O I-MISC I-VP I-MISC O
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-VP I-MISC O I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC O I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-VP O O
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-VP O O O O
3-GRAM  8       O O O I-NP I-PER B-NP
3-GRAM  13      O I-NP I-PER B-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  2       I-PER B-NP O I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  17      I-LOC I-NP O B-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  258     O I-NP O O O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  165     O O O I-ADVP O I-NP
3-GRAM  198     O I-ADVP O I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  652     O I-NP O I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  244     O I-NP O I-ADVP O I-VP
3-GRAM  183     O I-VP O I-VP O I-PRT
3-GRAM  138     O I-VP O I-PRT O I-PP
3-GRAM  128     O I-PRT O I-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  217     O I-NP O I-PP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  66      O I-PP I-PER I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  2553    I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP O O
3-GRAM  708     I-PER I-NP O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  82      O I-VP O I-PP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  28      O I-PP I-PER I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  27      O B-NP O I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  40      O I-NP O I-ADJP O I-NP
3-GRAM  29      O I-ADJP O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  421     O I-NP O O I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  102     O O I-LOC I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  27      I-LOC I-NP O I-VP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  38      O I-VP I-LOC I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  66      O I-NP O I-NP I-LOC I-VP
3-GRAM  66      O I-NP I-LOC I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  16      I-LOC I-VP O I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  73      O I-NP I-LOC I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  430     I-LOC I-NP O I-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  72      O I-NP O I-VP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  71      O I-VP I-LOC I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  24      I-LOC I-NP O I-PP O I-VP
3-GRAM  322     O I-PP O I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  368     O I-PP O I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  430     O I-NP I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  121     I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  260     O I-PP I-LOC I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  6       I-LOC I-NP O I-PP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  92      I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  47      O B-NP O I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  9       O B-NP O I-VP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  44      O I-VP I-LOC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  242     O I-NP O I-VP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  50      O I-ADVP O I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  181     I-LOC I-NP O O I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1134    I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  134     I-ORG I-NP O I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  59      I-PER I-NP O I-VP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  48      O I-VP I-ORG I-NP O O
3-GRAM  117     I-ORG I-NP O O O O
3-GRAM  236     I-LOC I-NP O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  130     I-LOC I-NP O O I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1209    O O I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  46      I-PER I-NP O O O I-PP
3-GRAM  30      O O O I-PP O I-VP
3-GRAM  108     O I-PP O I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  60      O O O I-ADVP O I-VP
3-GRAM  204     O I-ADVP O I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  41      O I-NP O I-VP O B-VP
3-GRAM  109     O I-VP O B-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  29      O B-VP O I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  23      O I-NP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG B-NP
3-GRAM  6       I-ORG B-NP I-ORG I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  11      I-ORG I-NP O I-VP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  28      I-PER I-NP O I-PP O I-VP
3-GRAM  38      O I-PP O I-VP O O
3-GRAM  50      O I-NP O B-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  10      O B-NP I-ORG I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  32      I-ORG I-NP O I-VP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  62      O I-VP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  122     I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  196     I-ORG I-NP O I-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  32      O I-NP O I-PP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  18      O I-PP O I-ADVP O I-NP
3-GRAM  188     O I-NP O I-ADVP O I-PP
3-GRAM  460     O I-ADVP O I-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1059    I-LOC I-NP O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  6       O O O I-NP I-LOC B-NP
3-GRAM  13      O I-NP I-LOC B-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  2       I-LOC B-NP O I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  359     O I-NP I-LOC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  73      O I-VP O I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  669     O O O I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  185     O I-NP I-PER I-NP O O
3-GRAM  83      O I-VP O I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  66      O I-ADVP O I-PP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  7       I-LOC I-NP O O O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  52      O I-VP O I-VP O B-VP
3-GRAM  87      O I-NP O I-VP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  350     O I-VP I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  42      O I-NP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-PP
3-GRAM  128     I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-PP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  4       I-ORG I-PP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-PP
3-GRAM  47      I-ORG I-PP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  26      I-ORG I-NP O O O I-PP
3-GRAM  287     O I-NP O I-ADVP O I-NP
3-GRAM  36      O I-ADVP O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  298     O I-NP O O I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  235     O O I-MISC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  127     I-LOC I-NP O I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  66      I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-PP
3-GRAM  18      O I-PP I-MISC I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  4       I-MISC I-NP O I-VP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  22      I-MISC I-NP O I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  242     O I-NP O I-ADVP O O
3-GRAM  3       O I-ADVP O O O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  71      O I-ADJP O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  793     O I-NP O I-VP O O
3-GRAM  350     I-ORG I-NP O I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  12      I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  7       I-ORG I-NP O I-ADVP O I-PP
3-GRAM  9       O I-ADVP O I-PP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  72      O I-NP O I-VP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  41      O I-VP I-ORG I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  863     I-ORG I-NP O I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  257     O I-NP I-ORG I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  99      O I-NP O I-PP O B-PP
3-GRAM  209     O I-PP O B-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  138     O B-PP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  48      O B-NP O I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  24      O I-NP O I-NP I-PER I-VP
3-GRAM  13      O I-NP I-PER I-VP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  8       I-PER I-VP I-PER I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  69      O I-NP O I-NP I-PER B-NP
3-GRAM  101     O I-NP I-PER B-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  26      I-PER B-NP I-PER I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  345     O O O I-VP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  75      O I-VP I-PER I-NP O O
3-GRAM  103     I-PER I-NP O O I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  14      I-ORG I-NP O O I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  21      O I-VP I-ORG I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  322     I-LOC I-NP O O I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  1434    O O I-LOC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  2       I-LOC I-NP O O I-LOC I-ADJP
3-GRAM  2       O O I-LOC I-ADJP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-LOC I-ADJP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  81      O I-NP O I-NP I-ORG I-VP
3-GRAM  8       O I-NP I-ORG I-VP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-VP I-ORG I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  221     I-ORG I-NP O I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  428     O O I-ORG I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  57      I-ORG I-NP O I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  48      O I-VP I-LOC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  17      O I-VP O O I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  75      I-ORG I-NP O O I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  13      O I-NP I-LOC I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  19      I-LOC I-NP O I-ADVP O I-NP
3-GRAM  5       I-LOC I-NP O I-VP O I-PRT
3-GRAM  188     O I-VP O I-PRT O I-NP
3-GRAM  27      O I-PRT O I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  158     O I-PP I-LOC I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  69      I-LOC I-NP O I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  440     O O O I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  435     I-LOC I-NP O O O I-VP
3-GRAM  42      O O O I-VP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  11      I-ORG I-NP O B-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  292     O I-VP O I-PP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-VP O I-VP O I-CONJP
3-GRAM  2       O I-VP O I-CONJP O I-CONJP
3-GRAM  17      O I-CONJP O I-CONJP O I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O I-CONJP O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  54      O I-NP O B-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  42      O B-NP I-MISC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  44      O I-VP O I-ADVP O I-VP
3-GRAM  93      O I-ADVP O I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  4       I-MISC I-NP O I-VP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  4       I-LOC I-NP O I-VP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  360     O I-NP I-PER I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  142     O I-PRT O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  163     O I-PP I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  59      O O O I-PP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  170     O I-VP O I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  11      O I-VP O I-SBAR I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  33      O I-SBAR I-LOC I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  14      O I-VP O O I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  122     I-MISC I-NP O I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  420     I-PER I-NP O O I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  19      I-PER I-NP O I-VP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  17      I-LOC I-NP O I-VP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  171     O I-VP O I-ADJP O I-PP
3-GRAM  279     O I-ADJP O I-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  49      O O O O I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  3       I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP B-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP B-LOC I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       B-LOC I-NP O I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  271     I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  81      O I-VP O I-PP O B-PP
3-GRAM  15      O I-PP O B-PP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O B-PP I-LOC I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  63      O I-ADJP O I-ADJP O O
3-GRAM  51      O O O I-VP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  295     O I-VP O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  10      O I-ADJP O I-ADJP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  39      O I-ADJP O I-SBAR O I-NP
3-GRAM  12      O I-SBAR O I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  390     O O O O I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  190     I-PER I-NP O I-VP O O
3-GRAM  123     O I-NP O O O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  74      O O I-LOC I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  43      I-LOC I-NP O B-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  67      O B-NP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  186     I-ORG I-NP O I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  24      O O O I-VP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  168     I-PER I-NP O I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  46      O I-NP I-PER I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  13      O I-ADVP O I-VP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  25      O I-VP O I-SBAR I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  44      O I-SBAR I-PER I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  66      I-LOC I-NP O I-PP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  102     O O O I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  430     I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  190     O I-VP O I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  18      O B-NP O I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  29      O I-NP O I-SBAR I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  79      O I-PP O I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  435     O I-NP I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  363     I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  33      O I-VP O O O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  25      O O O I-ADJP O O
3-GRAM  23      O B-PP O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  188     O O O I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  81      I-MISC I-NP O I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  143     I-PER I-NP O O O I-VP
3-GRAM  204     O I-VP O O O O
3-GRAM  46      O I-NP O I-PP O I-PP
3-GRAM  70      O I-PP O I-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  17      I-LOC I-NP O B-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  3       I-MISC I-NP O I-NP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  47      I-ORG I-PP I-ORG I-NP O O
3-GRAM  40      I-ORG I-NP O O I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  253     I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  116     O I-NP I-MISC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  26      O O I-MISC I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  2       I-MISC I-NP O I-VP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  24      O I-SBAR O I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  25      O I-NP I-MISC I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  4       I-MISC I-NP I-ORG I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  279     O I-PP I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  158     I-LOC I-NP O O O O
3-GRAM  56      I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  9       I-MISC I-NP O I-VP O O
3-GRAM  17      I-LOC I-NP O I-ADVP O I-VP
3-GRAM  86      O I-PP I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  206     O I-NP I-ORG I-NP O O
3-GRAM  238     O I-VP O I-ADVP O I-PP
3-GRAM  50      O I-VP O I-VP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  60      O I-VP I-ORG I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  91      I-ORG I-NP O I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  115     I-LOC I-NP O I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  88      I-MISC I-NP O I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  8       I-LOC I-NP O I-VP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  60      I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  92      I-MISC I-NP O I-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O I-ADJP O I-PP O I-PP
3-GRAM  542     I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  39      I-PER I-NP O I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  54      I-PER I-NP O I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  130     O I-VP O I-ADVP O O
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP O I-SBAR I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  17      O I-PP O I-VP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  43      O I-VP I-PER I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  19      O I-NP I-PER I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  27      I-PER I-NP O I-ADVP O I-VP
3-GRAM  31      I-MISC I-NP O I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  370     I-ORG I-NP O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  87      I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  37      I-PER I-NP O I-VP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  101     O I-VP O I-PP O I-VP
3-GRAM  6       O O O I-SBAR I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  22      O I-VP O I-ADJP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  31      O I-SBAR O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  81      I-PER I-NP O I-PP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  78      I-LOC I-NP O I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  47      I-MISC I-NP O I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  21      O I-PP I-PER I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  111     I-LOC I-NP O O O I-PP
3-GRAM  10      O O O I-PP O I-PP
3-GRAM  8       O I-PP O I-PP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  23      O O I-PER I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  21      O I-PP O I-VP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  77      O I-PP I-PER I-NP O O
3-GRAM  127     O I-VP O I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O O I-MISC I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-MISC I-NP I-LOC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  82      O I-NP O I-VP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  85      I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  49      I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  3       I-LOC I-NP O I-NP I-LOC B-NP
3-GRAM  5       O I-NP I-LOC B-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  3       I-LOC B-NP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  14      I-ORG I-NP O O O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  288     O I-VP O I-VP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  18      I-MISC I-NP O I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  24      O O O O O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  5       O O O I-ADVP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  6       O I-ADVP I-LOC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  132     O I-PP O I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O O O I-NP I-MISC B-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-NP I-MISC B-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  6       I-MISC B-NP O I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  67      O O O I-VP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  45      I-MISC I-NP O O O I-VP
3-GRAM  357     O O O I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  25      O I-NP I-MISC I-NP B-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  13      I-MISC I-NP B-MISC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  7       B-MISC I-NP O I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  96      I-MISC I-NP O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  6       O O O I-SBAR O I-VP
3-GRAM  12      O I-SBAR O I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  52      I-LOC I-NP O B-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  13      O B-NP I-PER I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  22      I-PER I-NP O I-VP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O B-NP I-PER I-NP O O
3-GRAM  6       I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-NP O I-SBAR I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O I-VP I-PER I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  12      I-PER I-NP O I-SBAR O I-NP
3-GRAM  52      O I-SBAR O I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  7       I-MISC I-NP I-ORG I-NP O O
3-GRAM  27      O I-VP O I-PP O O
3-GRAM  4       O I-VP I-LOC I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  14      I-LOC I-NP O I-ADVP O I-PP
3-GRAM  57      O B-NP O I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-VP O I-PP I-LOC I-INTJ
3-GRAM  1       O I-PP I-LOC I-INTJ I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-INTJ I-LOC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  15      O I-NP O I-NP I-LOC I-PP
3-GRAM  3       O I-NP I-LOC I-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-LOC I-PP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  80      O I-PP I-ORG I-NP O O
3-GRAM  15      I-PER I-NP O O I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1329    I-PER I-NP O O I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-VP O B-VP O O
3-GRAM  43      I-LOC I-NP O I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  34      O I-VP O I-NP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  56      O I-NP O I-ADJP O O
3-GRAM  44      O I-NP O B-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O B-NP O I-PP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  24      O I-PP I-ORG I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  88      O I-PP O I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  194     O I-ADVP O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  5       O I-NP O I-NP O I-INTJ
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP O I-INTJ O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O I-INTJ O I-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  13      O I-PP O I-ADVP O I-PP
3-GRAM  15      O I-VP O I-SBAR O I-PP
3-GRAM  20      O I-SBAR O I-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  86      O I-NP O B-NP O O
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-VP I-PER I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  18      I-PER I-NP O B-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  6       O B-NP O I-VP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  141     I-ORG I-NP O O O I-VP
3-GRAM  2       O O I-ORG I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  5       I-ORG I-NP I-MISC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  50      O I-PP I-ORG I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  10      I-ORG I-NP O B-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  11      O O O I-PP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  6       O I-NP O O O I-INTJ
3-GRAM  2       O O O I-INTJ O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-INTJ O I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  49      O I-VP O O O I-PP
3-GRAM  47      O O O I-PP O B-PP
3-GRAM  66      I-ORG I-NP O I-VP O O
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-PP I-ORG I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  6       I-ORG I-NP O I-ADVP O I-NP
3-GRAM  8       O I-NP O I-ADVP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  9       O I-ADVP I-LOC I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  33      O I-NP I-MISC I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  369     O O I-LOC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  34      O I-NP O B-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  17      O B-NP O B-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  56      O I-VP O I-ADVP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  32      O I-ADVP O I-ADVP O I-PP
3-GRAM  4       O I-ADVP O I-PP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  19      O I-PP O I-ADJP O O
3-GRAM  64      O I-ADJP O O O O
3-GRAM  7       O I-VP O I-SBAR O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       O I-SBAR O I-ADVP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  6       O I-ADVP O I-ADVP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  14      O I-ADVP O I-ADVP O I-VP
3-GRAM  26      O B-NP O I-VP O O
3-GRAM  36      O I-ADVP O I-ADVP O O
3-GRAM  17      O I-ADJP O I-ADJP O I-VP
3-GRAM  5       I-ORG I-NP O I-VP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  16      I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-PP
3-GRAM  34      I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-PP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  13      I-MISC I-PP I-MISC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  10      I-MISC I-PP I-MISC I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  4       O I-NP I-LOC B-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  2       I-LOC B-NP O I-SBAR O I-NP
3-GRAM  225     O O I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  3       I-PER I-NP O I-NP I-PER B-NP
3-GRAM  62      I-PER B-NP I-PER I-NP O O
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP O I-INTJ
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-NP O I-INTJ O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-INTJ O I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  71      I-LOC I-NP O I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  18      I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP I-MISC B-NP
3-GRAM  8       I-MISC I-NP I-MISC B-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  3       I-MISC B-NP O I-VP O O
3-GRAM  7       O I-NP I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-VP
3-GRAM  7       I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-VP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  3       I-MISC I-VP I-MISC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  257     O O I-PER I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  343     I-PER I-NP O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  30      O B-NP I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-VP I-PER I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  13      O I-NP O I-NP I-PER I-ADJP
3-GRAM  12      O I-NP I-PER I-ADJP O O
3-GRAM  10      I-PER I-ADJP O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O B-NP I-MISC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  11      I-MISC I-NP O O I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  3       I-PER I-NP O O O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  16      O O O I-ADJP O I-VP
3-GRAM  186     O I-VP O O O I-VP
3-GRAM  210     O O O I-VP O O
3-GRAM  17      O I-VP O I-ADVP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  45      O I-ADVP O I-SBAR O I-NP
3-GRAM  58      O O O I-PP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP O I-PP I-PER I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PP I-PER I-VP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  10      I-PER I-VP I-PER I-NP O O
3-GRAM  108     O O O O O O
3-GRAM  11      O I-NP O O I-PER I-VP
3-GRAM  4       O O I-PER I-VP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  30      O B-NP O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  5       O O O I-PP O O
3-GRAM  106     O O O I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  109     O O O I-ADVP O O
3-GRAM  71      O I-ADVP O O O I-VP
3-GRAM  4       I-PER B-NP I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  78      I-LOC I-NP O O O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  8       O I-PP O I-VP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-ORG I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-VP O I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PP O I-VP I-ORG I-VP
3-GRAM  2       O I-VP I-ORG I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  2       I-ORG I-VP O I-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  9       O O O O O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  132     O I-NP O I-VP O I-PRT
3-GRAM  31      O I-PP I-ORG I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  13      O I-ADVP O O O I-PP
3-GRAM  143     O O I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  9       I-MISC I-NP I-MISC B-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  8       I-MISC B-NP O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  19      I-MISC I-NP B-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  9       B-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  77      O I-VP O I-PRT O O
3-GRAM  20      O I-PRT O O I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  17      I-LOC I-NP O O I-ORG I-VP
3-GRAM  29      O O I-ORG I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  18      I-ORG I-VP O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  19      O I-PRT O O O O
3-GRAM  1       O O O O I-ORG I-INTJ
3-GRAM  3       O O I-ORG I-INTJ O O
3-GRAM  14      O I-PRT O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  5       I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP O I-LST
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-NP O I-LST O O
3-GRAM  6       O I-LST O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  35      I-LOC I-NP O I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  9       O O I-LOC I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  22      O I-ADVP O I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  49      O I-VP O O I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  9       I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  6       I-PER I-NP O I-ADVP O O
3-GRAM  15      O I-ADVP O O I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  41      I-PER I-NP O I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  98      O O I-PER I-NP O O
3-GRAM  17      I-ORG I-NP O B-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  67      O B-NP I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  11      I-ORG I-NP O I-NP I-PER B-NP
3-GRAM  47      O I-NP O I-ADVP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  11      O I-NP O I-NP I-PER I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-PER I-ADVP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-ADVP I-PER I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  25      I-PER I-NP O I-VP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  42      O O I-ORG I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  6       I-MISC I-NP O I-VP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  6       O I-NP O I-NP I-MISC O
3-GRAM  6       O I-NP I-MISC O I-MISC I-PRT
3-GRAM  6       I-MISC O I-MISC I-PRT O O
3-GRAM  50      I-LOC I-VP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  6       O O O I-ADVP O I-LST
3-GRAM  6       O I-ADVP O I-LST O I-NP
3-GRAM  19      O I-LST O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADVP O I-NP I-PER I-PP
3-GRAM  3       O I-NP I-PER I-PP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-PER I-PP I-PER I-NP O O
3-GRAM  23      O I-NP O I-NP I-ORG B-NP
3-GRAM  11      O I-NP I-ORG B-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  5       I-ORG B-NP O I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  6       I-PER I-NP O I-PP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O O I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-PRT
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-PRT I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-PRT I-MISC I-NP I-MISC B-NP
3-GRAM  14      I-MISC I-NP I-MISC B-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  6       I-MISC B-NP I-MISC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  6       I-MISC I-NP O I-VP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  2       O O I-ORG I-VP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  5       I-ORG I-VP I-ORG I-NP O O
3-GRAM  5       O O O I-NP O I-LST
3-GRAM  4       O I-NP O I-LST O I-NP
3-GRAM  9       I-ORG I-NP O I-VP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  36      O I-PP I-MISC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  11      I-MISC I-NP O O I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  9       O I-NP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-VP O O
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-VP O O I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  4       I-ORG I-VP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  4       I-PER I-NP O I-LST O I-NP
3-GRAM  13      O I-NP O O O I-LST
3-GRAM  6       O O O I-LST O O
3-GRAM  41      I-ORG I-NP O I-PP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  11      O O O I-PP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-NP O B-NP I-ORG B-NP
3-GRAM  1       O B-NP I-ORG B-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  12      I-ORG B-NP O I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  3       I-ORG I-NP O I-NP I-ORG I-INTJ
3-GRAM  5       O I-NP I-ORG I-INTJ O I-NP
3-GRAM  3       I-ORG I-INTJ O I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  15      I-ORG I-NP O B-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  6       O O I-PER I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-VP O I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  1       O B-NP I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-PRT
3-GRAM  3       I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-PRT O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-MISC I-PRT O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  66      O I-ADVP O I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  15      O I-PP O I-VP O I-PRT
3-GRAM  30      I-PER I-NP O O O O
3-GRAM  50      O I-VP O I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  14      O I-NP O B-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  15      O I-ADVP O I-PP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  11      O O I-MISC I-NP I-MISC O
3-GRAM  10      I-MISC I-NP I-MISC O O I-NP
3-GRAM  4       I-MISC O O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  2       I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  22      I-MISC I-VP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-VP I-PER I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-NP I-MISC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  60      I-PER I-NP O O I-LOC O
3-GRAM  62      O O I-LOC O O O
3-GRAM  5       I-LOC O O O O I-VP
3-GRAM  8       I-LOC O O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O I-NP O I-NP I-PER O
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-PER O O O
3-GRAM  1       I-PER O O O I-LOC O
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADVP O I-NP I-PER I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP O O I-PER I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O O I-PER I-VP I-PER O
3-GRAM  2       I-PER I-VP I-PER O O O
3-GRAM  6       I-PER O O O I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-PP I-PER I-NP I-PER I-VP
3-GRAM  3       I-PER I-NP I-PER I-VP O O
3-GRAM  2       I-PER I-VP O O I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  11      O I-NP O I-PP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PP O I-ADJP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-ADJP I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  10      O O I-LOC I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  7       I-LOC I-NP O I-PP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  8       I-LOC I-VP O I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  6       I-ORG I-NP O I-PP O I-VP
3-GRAM  22      I-LOC I-NP O B-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  13      O B-NP I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  23      I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  24      I-MISC I-NP O B-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  23      O I-PP O O O O
3-GRAM  102     O I-NP I-ORG I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  83      I-ORG I-VP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  53      I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  46      I-MISC I-NP I-ORG I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  97      I-ORG I-NP O I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  56      O I-NP I-LOC I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  70      I-LOC I-NP I-ORG I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  4       I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP I-ORG I-VP
3-GRAM  4       I-LOC I-NP I-ORG I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  4       I-ORG I-VP O I-VP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O I-VP I-LOC I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  6       I-ORG I-NP O I-NP I-LOC I-VP
3-GRAM  7       O I-NP I-LOC I-VP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  5       I-LOC I-VP I-LOC I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  23      O I-NP I-LOC I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  16      I-LOC I-NP I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  11      I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  22      I-MISC I-NP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  23      I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  26      I-ORG I-NP I-ORG B-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  25      I-ORG I-NP O I-NP I-ORG I-VP
3-GRAM  33      I-ORG I-VP O I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  14      I-ORG I-NP O I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-ORG I-VP O O
3-GRAM  2       O I-PP O O I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  9       O I-VP O I-ADVP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  21      O I-ADVP I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  12      O B-NP O B-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  44      O I-NP I-ORG I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  2       O B-NP O I-VP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  25      I-PER I-NP O I-VP O I-PRT
3-GRAM  60      O O O I-VP O I-PRT
3-GRAM  4       O I-NP I-MISC I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  6       I-MISC I-NP O I-SBAR O I-NP
3-GRAM  16      O I-NP O I-NP O I-PRT
3-GRAM  3       O I-NP O I-PRT O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PRT O I-VP O I-PRT
3-GRAM  5       O I-VP O I-PRT I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  5       O I-PRT I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  30      O I-VP I-ORG I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  22      O I-NP O O I-MISC I-VP
3-GRAM  22      O O I-MISC I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP O I-NP I-ORG I-ADVP
3-GRAM  4       O I-NP I-ORG I-ADVP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-ADVP O I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  7       O I-VP O B-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  2       O B-VP O I-PP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  12      O I-NP O B-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  22      O B-NP I-LOC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  11      O I-VP O I-PRT O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  5       O I-PRT O I-ADVP O O
3-GRAM  7       I-MISC O O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  5       O O I-LOC I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  3       O O I-PER I-NP I-PER I-ADVP
3-GRAM  2       I-PER I-NP I-PER I-ADVP O O
3-GRAM  2       I-PER I-ADVP O O I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  79      O O O I-ADVP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O I-VP O O O I-LST
3-GRAM  11      O I-NP O I-NP I-LOC B-NP
3-GRAM  24      O I-NP O B-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  19      O B-NP O I-ADVP O I-VP
3-GRAM  5       O I-ADVP O I-VP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  21      O I-NP O I-SBAR O I-VP
3-GRAM  15      O I-SBAR O I-VP O O
3-GRAM  28      O O O I-NP I-MISC O
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-MISC O O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC O O I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  12      O I-ADVP O I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  11      I-MISC I-NP O I-NP I-PER B-NP
3-GRAM  3       O I-NP O O I-ORG I-PP
3-GRAM  2       O O I-ORG I-PP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  7       O I-NP O I-NP I-ORG I-PP
3-GRAM  3       O I-NP I-ORG I-PP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADVP O O I-ORG I-PP
3-GRAM  8       O I-PP I-MISC I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  30      O I-NP O I-ADJP O I-VP
3-GRAM  12      O I-ADJP O I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O I-ADVP O I-VP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  29      O I-VP O I-ADVP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  13      O I-ADVP O I-ADJP O O
3-GRAM  5       O I-ADJP O O O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  2       O O O I-ADVP O B-ADVP
3-GRAM  6       O I-ADVP O B-ADVP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O B-ADVP O I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  16      O I-VP O I-SBAR I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  10      O I-SBAR I-ORG I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  22      O I-VP O I-PP O I-PP
3-GRAM  7       O B-PP O I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  4       I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-PP
3-GRAM  10      I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-PP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-PP I-LOC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP O I-SBAR O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  3       O I-SBAR O I-ADJP O O
3-GRAM  4       O I-VP O B-VP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  3       O B-VP O I-ADVP O I-NP
3-GRAM  13      O B-NP O I-VP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  5       O I-ADVP O O I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  24      O I-VP O B-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  14      O B-VP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  49      O O O O O I-PP
3-GRAM  4       O O O I-PP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  6       I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP I-MISC O
3-GRAM  5       I-MISC I-NP I-MISC O I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  3       I-MISC O I-MISC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  15      O I-ADVP O I-PP O I-VP
3-GRAM  11      O I-PP O I-PP O I-PP
3-GRAM  46      O I-NP O O O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  4       O I-ADJP O O O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  18      O O O I-ADJP O I-NP
3-GRAM  43      O O O O I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  7       O I-ADVP O I-VP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  1       O I-SBAR I-PER I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  5       I-PER I-NP O I-PP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  20      I-PER I-NP I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-SBAR O I-VP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  14      O I-NP I-MISC I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  10      O B-NP O I-VP O I-PRT
3-GRAM  6       O I-VP O I-PRT I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PRT I-PER I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  34      O I-SBAR O I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  3       O I-PP I-PER I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-NP O I-ADVP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  16      O I-ADVP O I-ADVP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  13      O I-PP I-MISC I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  57      I-MISC I-NP I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  6       I-PER I-NP O O O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  14      I-PER I-NP O I-VP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  8       O I-VP I-MISC I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  24      O I-NP I-MISC I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  24      O I-ADVP O I-ADVP O I-NP
3-GRAM  3       I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  28      O I-PP I-PER I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  18      I-MISC I-NP O I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O O I-PER I-NP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-NP O I-ADJP O O
3-GRAM  3       O I-ADJP O O I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O B-VP O I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  39      I-LOC I-NP O O I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  6       O O I-MISC I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  5       I-PER B-NP I-PER I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  7       O I-ADVP O I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  17      O O O I-ADJP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  26      O B-NP O I-VP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  2       I-MISC I-NP O I-VP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-NP O I-PP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  31      O I-ADVP O I-VP O O
3-GRAM  29      O I-VP O O O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  8       O O O I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  24      O I-PP O O O I-VP
3-GRAM  3       O I-PP I-LOC I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  26      O I-ADJP O O O I-VP
3-GRAM  2       I-MISC I-NP O I-NP I-LOC B-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC B-NP O I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O B-NP O I-ADVP O I-PP
3-GRAM  18      O I-VP O I-NP O I-PRT
3-GRAM  17      O I-NP O I-PRT O O
3-GRAM  9       O I-VP O I-ADJP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  5       O I-ADJP O I-ADVP O I-NP
3-GRAM  5       O I-PRT O I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  11      O B-NP O O O I-VP
3-GRAM  6       O O O O O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  7       I-ORG I-NP O I-NP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  3       O I-ADJP O I-PP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-PP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG B-NP
3-GRAM  13      I-ORG B-NP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  19      O I-NP O I-NP I-LOC I-ADVP
3-GRAM  16      O I-NP I-LOC I-ADVP O I-NP
3-GRAM  6       I-LOC I-ADVP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O I-SBAR I-LOC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  8       O I-PP O I-VP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  27      O I-NP I-MISC O O O
3-GRAM  9       I-MISC O O O O I-PP
3-GRAM  2       O B-NP O B-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O O I-MISC I-NP B-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  6       I-LOC I-ADVP O I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O I-NP O I-NP I-ORG O
3-GRAM  2       O I-NP I-ORG O O O
3-GRAM  4       I-ORG O O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-ORG I-PP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG O
3-GRAM  45      I-ORG I-NP I-ORG O I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  17      I-ORG O I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  7       O I-PP O B-PP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O B-PP I-PER I-NP O O
3-GRAM  9       O I-PRT O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  4       O I-VP O I-PRT I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O I-PRT I-MISC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  9       O I-ADJP O I-PP O B-PP
3-GRAM  4       O I-ADVP O O O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  5       O I-NP O I-NP I-LOC I-INTJ
3-GRAM  5       O I-NP I-LOC I-INTJ O O
3-GRAM  5       I-LOC I-INTJ O O I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  5       O I-VP I-PER I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  27      O I-NP O I-ADVP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  17      O I-ADVP I-PER I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  5       I-PER B-NP O I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  14      O I-ADVP O I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  24      O I-VP O I-PRT O I-VP
3-GRAM  13      O I-PRT O I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  4       O I-VP O I-NP I-MISC B-NP
3-GRAM  9       O I-NP I-MISC B-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-MISC B-NP O I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  11      O I-NP O I-SBAR O O
3-GRAM  7       O I-SBAR O O O I-VP
3-GRAM  3       I-LOC I-VP O I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  3       I-PER I-NP O I-VP O B-VP
3-GRAM  3       O B-VP O I-VP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  15      I-LOC I-NP O I-VP O O
3-GRAM  8       O B-NP O I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-NP I-MISC I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  14      O I-NP O I-ADVP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  4       I-PER I-VP O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O I-NP I-PER I-VP O O
3-GRAM  10      O B-NP O O O O
3-GRAM  11      O I-ADVP O I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-NP I-ORG I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADVP O I-SBAR I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O B-PP I-LOC I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  7       O I-ADVP O I-ADJP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  2       O I-NP I-PER I-NP I-PER I-ADJP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-NP I-PER I-ADJP O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-ADJP O I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  10      O I-VP I-MISC I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  2       O I-ADVP O I-SBAR O I-VP
3-GRAM  12      O I-SBAR O I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  6       O I-NP O B-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  5       O B-NP O I-SBAR O I-NP
3-GRAM  29      O I-VP I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  6       O I-NP I-MISC I-NP I-MISC B-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC B-NP I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  23      O I-NP O I-SBAR I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  5       O I-VP I-ORG I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  3       I-ORG I-NP O I-SBAR I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  8       O O O I-SBAR O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  18      O I-SBAR O I-SBAR O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-NP O B-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  8       O I-ADVP O I-VP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  17      O I-ADVP O I-VP O I-PRT
3-GRAM  8       O I-ADVP O I-ADJP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADJP O I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  14      O I-PP O I-VP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PP O I-ADJP O I-PP
3-GRAM  4       O I-ADJP O O I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  5       O I-NP O I-SBAR O I-PP
3-GRAM  3       I-LOC I-NP I-MISC I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  10      I-PER I-NP I-LOC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  2       O I-VP I-LOC I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  8       I-LOC I-NP I-MISC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  11      I-MISC I-NP O I-PP O I-VP
3-GRAM  25      I-PER I-NP O I-VP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PRT O I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  4       I-PER I-NP O I-PP O O
3-GRAM  9       I-PER I-NP O I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  12      O O O I-VP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  5       O I-SBAR I-LOC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  12      O O O I-SBAR I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  4       I-PER I-NP O B-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O I-SBAR I-PER I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  3       O I-NP O O I-ORG I-INTJ
3-GRAM  1       O O I-ORG I-INTJ O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-INTJ O I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  53      O I-ADVP O O O O
3-GRAM  3       O O O I-ADJP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  9       O I-ADJP O I-ADVP O O
3-GRAM  3       O I-ADJP O I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O B-NP I-MISC I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  4       O I-NP I-ORG B-NP O O
3-GRAM  2       I-LOC I-NP O B-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  7       O B-NP O I-ADVP O I-NP
3-GRAM  21      O I-ADVP O I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP O I-ADVP O I-PRT
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADVP O I-PRT O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-PRT O I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-ADVP O I-NP I-LOC I-VP
3-GRAM  4       I-LOC I-VP O I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  2       O I-PP I-ORG I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  11      I-ORG I-NP O I-SBAR O I-NP
3-GRAM  13      I-PER I-NP O B-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  32      O B-NP I-ORG I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  24      O I-PP I-LOC I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  8       I-LOC I-NP O I-ADVP O O
3-GRAM  8       O O O I-ADVP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  6       O I-ADJP O I-PP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O B-NP O B-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  3       I-LOC I-NP O I-VP O B-VP
3-GRAM  5       O I-SBAR I-LOC I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  2       O B-PP I-LOC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  4       I-MISC I-NP O O I-MISC O
3-GRAM  4       O O I-MISC O O O
3-GRAM  2       O I-VP O I-NP I-LOC B-NP
3-GRAM  8       I-LOC B-NP O I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  9       O I-NP I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-PP
3-GRAM  17      I-MISC I-NP O I-PP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  8       I-LOC I-NP O I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP O I-PP O B-PP
3-GRAM  15      O B-PP O I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O I-SBAR O I-PP O B-PP
3-GRAM  5       O O I-LOC I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  9       I-ORG I-PP I-ORG I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O O O I-INTJ O O
3-GRAM  1       O I-INTJ O O O O
3-GRAM  1       O I-VP O I-SBAR O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  2       O I-NP I-PER I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-VP O I-VP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-PER I-NP I-PER I-PP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-NP I-PER I-PP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-PP I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  10      O I-ADJP O O O I-PP
3-GRAM  3       O O I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-PP
3-GRAM  6       O I-PP O I-NP I-ORG B-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-NP I-ORG B-NP I-ORG I-PP
3-GRAM  2       I-ORG B-NP I-ORG I-PP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  6       O I-ADVP O I-PP O B-PP
3-GRAM  3       O O O I-SBAR O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O I-SBAR O I-PP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  6       O I-VP O I-ADVP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  7       O I-ADVP I-LOC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  24      O I-NP I-PER I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  2       O I-ADJP O I-SBAR O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADVP O I-VP O B-VP
3-GRAM  3       O I-VP O B-VP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  1       O B-VP O I-ADJP O O
3-GRAM  22      I-LOC I-NP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  17      I-ORG I-NP O I-VP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  2       O O O I-SBAR O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  21      I-LOC I-NP O I-VP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  4       I-LOC I-NP O I-SBAR O I-VP
3-GRAM  2       I-PER I-ADJP O O O I-VP
3-GRAM  11      I-MISC I-NP O O O I-PP
3-GRAM  12      O I-NP I-LOC I-PP I-LOC I-VP
3-GRAM  14      I-LOC I-PP I-LOC I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  6       O B-VP O I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  4       O I-PP I-MISC I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O B-VP O I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  5       O I-NP O O I-LOC I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O O I-LOC I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP O O I-LOC I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O O I-LOC I-PP I-LOC I-VP
3-GRAM  3       I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  8       O O I-LOC I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O B-NP I-LOC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  5       O B-NP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O B-NP I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O I-VP O I-NP O I-CONJP
3-GRAM  12      O I-NP O I-CONJP O I-CONJP
3-GRAM  11      O I-CONJP O I-CONJP O I-CONJP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-NP O I-VP O B-VP
3-GRAM  1       O B-VP O O O I-VP
3-GRAM  3       O I-VP O I-NP I-PER B-NP
3-GRAM  5       I-MISC I-PP I-MISC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O O O I-INTJ O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O I-INTJ O I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  7       O I-NP O I-ADVP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  9       O I-ADVP I-MISC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  5       O I-SBAR O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  3       I-MISC I-NP I-MISC O I-MISC I-ADJP
3-GRAM  3       I-MISC O I-MISC I-ADJP O O
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-ADJP O O O O
3-GRAM  3       I-MISC I-NP I-ORG I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  2       I-MISC I-ADJP O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O I-PP O O I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC O I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O O I-MISC I-NP I-MISC B-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC B-NP I-MISC I-NP I-MISC B-NP
3-GRAM  4       I-MISC B-NP I-MISC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  1       O I-PRT O O I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-ADJP O O O I-PP
3-GRAM  2       I-MISC O O O O I-VP
3-GRAM  9       O I-NP I-PER I-ADVP O O
3-GRAM  7       I-PER I-ADVP O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  20      I-MISC O O O O O
3-GRAM  3       O I-NP O I-NP I-LOC I-ADJP
3-GRAM  3       O I-NP I-LOC I-ADJP O O
3-GRAM  3       I-LOC I-ADJP O O I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  37      I-LOC O O O I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O I-NP O O I-PER O
3-GRAM  3       O O I-PER O I-PER O
3-GRAM  2       I-PER O I-PER O O O
3-GRAM  2       I-PER O O O O O
3-GRAM  3       O I-SBAR O I-PP O I-VP
3-GRAM  3       O I-NP I-PER I-NP I-PER I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-NP I-PER I-ADVP O I-CONJP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-ADVP O I-CONJP O I-PRT
3-GRAM  1       O I-CONJP O I-PRT O I-NP
3-GRAM  7       O I-PRT O I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O I-NP O O I-PER I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       O O I-PER I-ADVP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-ADVP O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  9       O I-NP O I-PRT O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PP O I-PP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-SBAR O I-NP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  10      O I-SBAR O I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  6       O O O I-PP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  4       O I-ADVP O I-ADJP O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PRT O O O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  1       O I-SBAR O I-ADJP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADJP O I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  1       O I-SBAR I-PER I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  3       O I-NP O I-ADVP O B-ADVP
3-GRAM  2       O I-ADVP O B-ADVP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  2       O B-ADVP O I-SBAR O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O B-PP I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  8       O I-SBAR I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O I-SBAR O I-ADVP O I-PP
3-GRAM  6       O I-PP O B-PP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O B-PP I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O O O I-ADJP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-ADJP I-MISC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  6       I-ORG I-VP O I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  12      O I-VP O O I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  5       I-PER I-VP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O I-PRT I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  8       O I-SBAR O I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  13      O I-NP O I-SBAR I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  5       O I-SBAR I-ORG I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  6       O O I-ORG I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  25      I-ORG I-NP O I-ADVP O I-VP
3-GRAM  4       I-MISC I-NP O I-VP O I-PRT
3-GRAM  1       I-PER B-NP O I-VP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  4       I-LOC O O O I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  7       O B-NP O I-NP I-PER B-NP
3-GRAM  6       I-PER I-NP O I-ADVP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PRT I-PER I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  7       O I-ADVP O I-PP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-NP I-PER B-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  4       I-PER B-NP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  6       O I-PP I-PER I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  6       I-LOC I-NP O O O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADJP O I-NP I-PER B-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-PER B-NP I-PER O
3-GRAM  1       I-PER B-NP I-PER O O O
3-GRAM  2       I-PER I-NP O I-NP O I-PRT
3-GRAM  11      O I-NP O I-PRT O I-NP
3-GRAM  5       O I-PRT O I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-PP I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-PRT
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-PRT O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-PRT O I-VP O O
3-GRAM  6       O B-NP I-ORG I-NP O O
3-GRAM  2       O I-PRT O I-PP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-PP O I-PP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O I-PP I-MISC I-NP I-MISC B-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-PRT O I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O B-VP O I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  5       O B-NP O I-PP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC B-NP I-MISC I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADJP O I-ADVP O I-VP
3-GRAM  2       O B-VP O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  19      I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG O
3-GRAM  5       I-ORG O I-ORG I-NP O O
3-GRAM  14      O O O I-ADVP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  2       I-MISC I-NP O I-NP I-MISC B-NP
3-GRAM  8       I-MISC B-NP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-VP I-ORG I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  3       I-ORG I-NP I-MISC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  5       O I-ADVP O I-PP O I-PP
3-GRAM  9       I-ORG I-NP O I-VP O I-PRT
3-GRAM  5       O O O I-SBAR I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  21      O O O I-ADJP O I-PP
3-GRAM  17      O B-NP O I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-LOC I-NP O I-INTJ
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP O I-INTJ O O
3-GRAM  4       O I-INTJ O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  20      I-ORG I-PP I-ORG I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  13      I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  3       O O I-LOC I-VP O O
3-GRAM  3       I-LOC I-VP O O I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O O O I-ADJP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADJP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  11      I-ORG B-NP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-LOC I-NP I-ORG I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O B-NP O I-PP O O
3-GRAM  1       O I-PP O O I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O O I-MISC I-NP I-PER B-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-NP I-PER B-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  3       I-PER B-NP I-PER I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  5       O I-VP O I-PRT O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  4       O I-PRT O I-SBAR O I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O I-PRT O I-ADVP O I-PP
3-GRAM  2       O I-VP O I-PP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  7       O I-PP O I-SBAR O I-NP
3-GRAM  6       O I-NP O I-ADVP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADVP I-ORG I-NP O O
3-GRAM  4       O I-ADJP O I-VP O O
3-GRAM  11      O I-PP O I-ADVP O O
3-GRAM  4       O I-ADJP O I-ADVP O I-PP
3-GRAM  18      O I-VP I-MISC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  4       I-PER I-NP O B-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O B-NP O I-PP O I-PP
3-GRAM  5       O I-NP I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-PP
3-GRAM  4       I-LOC I-PP I-LOC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  9       O I-SBAR I-ORG I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  8       I-PER I-NP O I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-MISC I-NP O I-PP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O B-NP I-ORG I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  4       I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  2       I-MISC I-NP O I-ADVP O O
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG O I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-PP
3-GRAM  3       O I-PRT O I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-VP I-LOC I-NP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP O I-ADJP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  3       O I-PP O B-PP O B-PP
3-GRAM  2       O B-PP O B-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-ADJP O I-PP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  5       I-LOC I-PP I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG B-NP O I-VP O O
3-GRAM  3       O I-NP O I-NP I-PER I-INTJ
3-GRAM  3       O I-NP I-PER I-INTJ O O
3-GRAM  2       I-PER I-INTJ O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  11      O I-PRT O I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PRT O O O I-PP
3-GRAM  2       O I-PP I-ORG I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  6       I-ORG I-NP I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  3       I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O I-PRT O I-NP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  2       O O I-PER I-NP I-PER B-NP
3-GRAM  6       I-PER I-NP I-PER B-NP O O
3-GRAM  2       I-PER B-NP O O O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP O I-PP I-MISC I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PP I-MISC I-PP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  14      O B-NP O I-VP O B-VP
3-GRAM  3       O I-ADVP I-PER I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  7       O O O I-NP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  2       O I-PP O I-ADJP O I-NP
3-GRAM  12      O B-VP O I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  10      O I-ADVP O I-ADJP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PP O I-PP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  3       O I-PP O I-NP I-LOC B-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP I-ORG I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-NP O B-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  6       O B-PP O I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  6       O I-NP O I-NP I-ORG I-INTJ
3-GRAM  2       O I-NP I-ORG I-INTJ O O
3-GRAM  3       O I-ADVP O B-ADVP O I-PP
3-GRAM  3       O B-ADVP O I-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O B-VP O I-VP O I-PRT
3-GRAM  2       O I-VP I-LOC I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  7       O I-SBAR O I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  8       O I-NP O I-SBAR O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  13      O I-VP O I-ADVP O B-ADVP
3-GRAM  4       O B-ADVP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O B-VP O I-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  20      O B-VP O I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  8       O O O I-ADVP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  8       O I-VP O I-SBAR O B-SBAR
3-GRAM  8       O I-SBAR O B-SBAR O I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O B-SBAR O I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PP O I-ADVP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  3       O I-NP I-LOC I-ADVP O O
3-GRAM  3       I-LOC I-ADVP O O I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  16      O I-NP I-ORG I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-PP O I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  11      O I-NP I-ORG B-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O I-PP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG O
3-GRAM  3       O I-PRT O I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  11      I-ORG I-NP O I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADVP O I-SBAR I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-SBAR I-ORG I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  6       O I-SBAR I-MISC I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  8       O I-VP O I-SBAR I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-SBAR I-MISC I-NP I-MISC B-NP
3-GRAM  7       O O O I-ADVP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADVP O I-SBAR I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  5       O I-SBAR I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O B-VP O I-PP O I-VP
3-GRAM  7       O I-NP O I-NP O I-CONJP
3-GRAM  10      O I-CONJP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  5       O I-PP O I-NP I-PER B-NP
3-GRAM  7       O I-SBAR O I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O B-NP O I-VP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O I-NP O I-INTJ O O
3-GRAM  22      O I-VP I-PER I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  6       O I-PRT O O O I-VP
3-GRAM  2       O I-NP O I-PRT O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  39      O B-VP O I-VP O O
3-GRAM  1       O I-INTJ O O O I-PP
3-GRAM  4       O O O I-LST O I-LST
3-GRAM  4       O I-LST O I-LST O O
3-GRAM  3       I-ORG I-NP O B-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  3       O I-VP O B-VP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  3       O B-VP O I-SBAR O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-SBAR O I-ADVP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-PRT O I-ADVP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  2       I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP O I-CONJP
3-GRAM  3       I-ORG I-NP O I-CONJP O I-CONJP
3-GRAM  6       I-ORG I-NP O B-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  3       I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP I-LOC I-PP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-NP I-LOC I-PP I-LOC I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADJP O I-SBAR O O
3-GRAM  3       O I-SBAR O O O O
3-GRAM  5       O I-ADJP O I-ADJP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP O I-ADJP O I-CONJP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADJP O I-CONJP O I-CONJP
3-GRAM  1       O I-CONJP O I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  3       I-LOC I-NP O I-VP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O B-PP I-MISC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-VP O I-VP I-ORG I-VP
3-GRAM  2       O I-VP I-ORG I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  5       O B-PP O I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O I-PP O I-NP I-MISC B-NP
3-GRAM  4       O I-NP I-MISC B-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  4       I-MISC B-NP O I-SBAR O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADVP O O I-ORG I-VP
3-GRAM  3       O O I-ORG I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  3       I-ORG I-VP O I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-ORG I-NP O I-NP O I-PRT
3-GRAM  2       I-MISC I-NP O I-NP I-ORG B-NP
3-GRAM  3       I-ORG B-NP O I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  12      O O I-PER I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  15      I-PER I-NP O O O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       O I-SBAR I-MISC I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  40      O O O I-VP O B-VP
3-GRAM  2       I-LOC B-NP O I-SBAR O I-VP
3-GRAM  6       O B-NP O O O I-PP
3-GRAM  27      O I-PP O O O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  2       O I-PP O I-NP O I-PRT
3-GRAM  3       O I-SBAR I-ORG I-NP O O
3-GRAM  2       O I-NP I-ORG B-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG B-NP O I-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O I-PP O O O I-PP
3-GRAM  6       I-PER I-NP O I-ADVP O I-NP
3-GRAM  4       I-ORG I-NP O O O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  13      O I-SBAR I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  6       O I-NP O I-PP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  2       O I-PP O I-SBAR O I-VP
3-GRAM  12      O I-NP O O I-ORG I-VP
3-GRAM  3       O O I-PER I-NP I-PER I-VP
3-GRAM  3       I-PER I-NP I-PER I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-VP O I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  5       I-ORG I-NP O I-ADVP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  6       O I-ADVP I-ORG I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  7       I-ORG B-NP I-ORG I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O B-NP I-MISC I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  6       O I-ADVP I-ORG I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  4       I-ORG I-NP O I-NP I-ORG B-NP
3-GRAM  5       O I-NP I-ORG B-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG B-NP O I-NP I-ORG I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O O I-PER I-VP O O
3-GRAM  22      O I-NP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG O
3-GRAM  8       I-ORG O I-ORG I-NP I-ORG O
3-GRAM  6       I-ORG I-NP I-ORG O O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-ORG O O I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  6       I-ORG O O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-NP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-ADVP
3-GRAM  2       I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-ADVP O I-NP
3-GRAM  3       I-ORG I-ADVP O I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG O O I-NP I-ORG I-VP
3-GRAM  2       I-ORG I-NP I-ORG O I-ORG O
3-GRAM  2       I-ORG O I-ORG O I-ORG O
3-GRAM  2       I-ORG O I-ORG O O I-NP
3-GRAM  4       I-ORG I-ADVP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-NP I-LOC I-NP I-ORG I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-NP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-VP
3-GRAM  3       O I-PRT O I-PP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  11      O I-NP O I-NP I-ORG I-ADJP
3-GRAM  8       O I-NP I-ORG I-ADJP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-ORG I-ADJP O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  4       I-ORG I-ADJP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-ORG I-NP O I-NP I-ORG I-ADJP
3-GRAM  2       I-ORG I-ADJP O I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  6       I-ORG O I-ORG I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PRT O O O I-PRT
3-GRAM  3       O O O I-PRT O I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O B-NP O I-VP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC B-NP O I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  4       I-PER B-NP O I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP I-LOC I-VP
3-GRAM  2       I-PER I-NP I-LOC I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       B-MISC I-NP O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP O B-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  1       B-MISC I-NP O I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADJP I-MISC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  4       O I-PRT O I-PP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O B-NP O O O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       O O O O I-PER I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       O O I-PER I-ADVP O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-ADVP O I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP O I-NP I-ORG I-ADVP
3-GRAM  2       O I-ADVP O I-ADVP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  4       I-LOC I-NP O I-PP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       O B-NP I-MISC I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-PP I-LOC I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  2       I-PER I-NP O I-NP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  7       O I-NP O O O I-CONJP
3-GRAM  9       O O O I-CONJP O I-CONJP
3-GRAM  3       O I-CONJP O I-CONJP O I-PP
3-GRAM  4       O I-CONJP O I-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O I-NP I-PER I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  6       O I-NP I-LOC I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  4       I-PER I-NP O B-NP O O
3-GRAM  1       O I-SBAR O I-ADVP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  4       I-ORG I-NP O I-PP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O O I-MISC I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O B-PP I-LOC I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-VP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-VP
3-GRAM  5       I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-VP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-VP I-ORG I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP O I-NP I-PER B-NP
3-GRAM  1       O B-NP I-LOC I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  10      I-LOC I-NP O I-NP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADVP O I-SBAR O O
3-GRAM  2       O I-PRT O I-PP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  2       O I-PP O I-ADVP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  7       O I-SBAR I-PER I-NP O O
3-GRAM  2       I-LOC I-NP O I-ADVP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADJP O I-SBAR I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-ADVP I-PER I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O I-ADVP I-PER I-NP O O
3-GRAM  3       O I-NP I-ORG I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  10      O I-VP O I-SBAR O I-VP
3-GRAM  4       O I-VP I-MISC I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-CONJP O I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O B-PP I-PER I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  4       O I-SBAR I-PER I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-NP I-PER I-NP I-PER I-VP
3-GRAM  8       O B-NP O O I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  9       I-LOC O O O I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-PER I-ADVP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-PER I-ADVP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC O O O I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  8       I-ORG I-NP O B-NP O O
3-GRAM  1       O O I-ORG I-VP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-VP I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O O I-ORG I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  4       I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  3       I-PER I-NP O I-ADJP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O I-VP I-MISC I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  4       I-PER I-NP O I-PP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  5       O O I-PER I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-PER B-NP O O
3-GRAM  2       I-PER I-NP O I-PP O B-PP
3-GRAM  10      O O I-ORG I-NP I-ORG B-NP
3-GRAM  1       O O I-PER I-ADVP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-ADVP O I-ADVP O O
3-GRAM  3       O I-VP O B-VP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O B-VP I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-PER B-NP I-PER I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-VP O I-SBAR O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  2       O O I-LOC I-VP O I-INTJ
3-GRAM  2       I-LOC I-VP O I-INTJ I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  6       O I-INTJ I-LOC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC B-NP O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  7       O O I-LOC I-NP O I-INTJ
3-GRAM  5       I-LOC I-NP O I-INTJ I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-INTJ I-LOC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  2       O O I-ORG I-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-ORG I-PP O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  5       O I-NP I-ORG I-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  5       I-ORG I-PP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-ORG I-NP O I-NP I-ORG I-ADVP
3-GRAM  2       O O O O I-ORG I-ADVP
3-GRAM  2       O O I-ORG I-ADVP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC O O O O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-NP I-PER I-ADVP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-ADVP I-PER I-NP O O
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-NP O I-NP I-ORG I-PP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-VP I-LOC I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-LOC I-VP O I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PRT O I-ADVP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-VP O I-VP O I-INTJ
3-GRAM  1       O I-VP O I-INTJ I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-INTJ I-ORG I-NP O O
3-GRAM  5       I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-VP
3-GRAM  2       O I-NP I-ORG I-ADJP O O
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-ADJP O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-VP O I-ADVP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADVP I-ORG I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-PER B-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER B-NP O B-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  2       I-PER I-NP O I-SBAR I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-PP I-MISC I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  5       I-MISC I-NP O I-ADVP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PRT O I-VP O O
3-GRAM  5       O O I-ORG I-NP O I-INTJ
3-GRAM  5       I-ORG I-NP O I-INTJ I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-INTJ I-ORG I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       B-MISC I-NP O I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  3       I-ORG I-VP O I-NP I-ORG I-VP
3-GRAM  3       O O O O I-ORG I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  3       O I-NP I-PER I-NP I-PER B-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-PER I-NP I-PER B-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       B-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP B-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-VP O O I-PER I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-VP O I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  2       B-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-PER B-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER B-NP O I-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O I-INTJ I-ORG I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O B-PP O B-PP O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O B-PP O I-VP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O O I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-VP
3-GRAM  4       I-PER I-VP O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  2       I-MISC I-VP O I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-NP O I-PP O B-PP
3-GRAM  3       O I-ADJP O I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  5       O I-ADJP O I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADJP O I-ADVP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  2       O B-NP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG O
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-NP O O I-PER I-ADVP
3-GRAM  2       O O I-PER I-ADVP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-ADVP I-PER I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-NP O I-ADJP O O
3-GRAM  1       O I-VP O B-VP O B-VP
3-GRAM  1       O B-VP O B-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O I-VP O I-PP I-MISC O
3-GRAM  2       O I-PP I-MISC O O O
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-NP I-PER I-ADVP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-ADVP I-LOC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  5       O I-PP I-MISC I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  3       I-MISC I-NP I-LOC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  3       O I-PP O I-ADVP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADJP O I-VP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-PP O B-PP O O
3-GRAM  8       O I-VP I-MISC I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  4       O I-NP I-MISC I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP O I-VP I-ORG I-VP
3-GRAM  4       I-ORG I-NP O I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  3       O I-PP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-PP
3-GRAM  2       I-LOC I-NP O B-NP O O
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP O I-SBAR I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  5       I-MISC I-NP O O O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  2       O I-PP O I-PP O O
3-GRAM  1       O I-CONJP O I-CONJP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       O I-CONJP O I-ADVP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  4       O I-ADVP O I-PP O O
3-GRAM  1       O I-VP O I-ADJP O B-ADJP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADJP O B-ADJP O O
3-GRAM  5       O B-NP O I-NP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  2       I-MISC I-NP I-LOC I-NP I-LOC O
3-GRAM  2       I-LOC I-NP I-LOC O I-LOC O
3-GRAM  2       I-LOC O I-LOC O I-LOC O
3-GRAM  2       I-LOC O I-LOC O I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC O I-LOC I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  2       O O O I-ADVP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O B-PP O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-LOC O I-LOC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  1       O I-PP O I-ADJP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  5       O I-ADVP O I-VP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O I-ADVP O B-ADVP O I-VP
3-GRAM  2       O B-ADVP O I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PP I-ORG I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  2       O I-CONJP O I-CONJP O O
3-GRAM  1       O I-CONJP O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O I-VP I-ORG I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  2       I-PER B-NP O I-VP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PP O I-NP I-ORG I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-VP O I-NP I-PER B-NP
3-GRAM  4       I-MISC I-NP O O O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-VP O I-VP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  11      O B-NP O O I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-ORG I-NP O O I-ORG I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-NP O O I-ORG I-INTJ
3-GRAM  2       I-ORG I-INTJ O O I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-LOC B-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-LOC B-NP I-LOC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-LOC B-NP O I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  5       I-ORG I-VP I-ORG I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-ORG I-INTJ O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADVP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-NP O I-INTJ O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O I-INTJ O I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O I-PRT O I-PP O I-VP
3-GRAM  3       I-PER I-ADVP O O O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O I-VP O I-ADJP O I-PRT
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADJP O I-PRT O O
3-GRAM  1       O I-PRT O O O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  2       I-MISC I-NP O B-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  4       O I-ADVP O O O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  2       O O O I-SBAR I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-PER I-NP O I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       O I-VP O I-NP I-MISC O
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-MISC O O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP O I-VP I-PER I-VP
3-GRAM  2       O I-VP I-PER I-VP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PRT I-PER I-NP O O
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-INTJ O O O O
3-GRAM  2       O B-NP O I-PP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-VP I-LOC I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP I-PER I-NP O O
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADVP O I-ADVP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O I-ADVP O I-SBAR I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  4       I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-NP I-MISC I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  6       O B-PP O I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  3       O I-NP O I-PP I-MISC I-VP
3-GRAM  2       O I-PP I-MISC I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  2       I-MISC I-VP O I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  4       O I-VP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG B-NP
3-GRAM  2       O B-NP O I-PP O B-PP
3-GRAM  3       O O I-LOC I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  7       I-LOC I-NP I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O I-NP I-LOC I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-NP O O I-PER I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-VP O I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O O O I-NP O I-PRT
3-GRAM  3       O O O O I-PER I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O O I-PER I-VP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-VP O I-ADVP O O
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP O I-ADVP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP O B-NP I-MISC O
3-GRAM  1       O B-NP I-MISC O O O
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC O O O I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O I-VP O I-PP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  4       O I-NP O O I-ORG O
3-GRAM  2       O O I-ORG O O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-VP O I-ADJP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP I-LOC I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-NP I-LOC I-ADVP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-LOC I-ADVP O I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PRT O I-SBAR O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O B-PP O I-NP O I-CONJP
3-GRAM  4       O I-CONJP O I-CONJP O I-VP
3-GRAM  2       O I-CONJP O I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADJP O I-ADVP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O B-VP O I-VP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  1       O I-SBAR O I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  3       O I-NP O I-NP I-ORG I-SBAR
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-ORG I-SBAR O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-SBAR O I-VP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O I-NP O I-ADVP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  3       I-MISC I-NP I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-VP I-ORG I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-NP I-PER I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-ADJP O O O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC B-NP I-MISC I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  2       I-MISC I-NP I-PER I-NP O O
3-GRAM  8       I-ORG I-NP O O I-ORG O
3-GRAM  9       O O I-ORG O O O
3-GRAM  4       I-ORG O O O O I-VP
3-GRAM  2       I-MISC I-NP O O O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  3       O I-PP O I-SBAR I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADJP O I-ADJP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADJP I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  5       O I-PRT O I-PP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP O I-PRT O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  7       O I-PP O B-PP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O B-PP I-ORG I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  3       I-LOC I-NP O I-SBAR I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  6       O I-NP O I-NP I-MISC B-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-NP I-MISC B-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O I-NP O I-ADJP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  3       O O I-PER I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  2       I-PER I-VP O I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  8       O I-ADVP O O I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-ADVP O I-ADJP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  2       O I-ADJP O I-ADJP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADJP O I-NP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  2       I-PER I-NP O I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADJP I-PER I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  2       O I-NP O O O I-PRT
3-GRAM  7       O B-PP O I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-NP I-ORG I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-NP O I-PP O O
3-GRAM  2       O I-VP I-MISC I-NP I-MISC O
3-GRAM  3       O I-ADVP O I-ADVP O B-ADVP
3-GRAM  4       I-ORG I-PP I-ORG I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADJP O I-SBAR O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O B-NP I-LOC I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  2       I-MISC I-NP O I-ADVP O I-PP
3-GRAM  3       I-ORG O I-ORG I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP I-LOC B-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-NP I-LOC B-NP O O
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC B-NP O O I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O O I-ORG I-NP I-ORG O
3-GRAM  3       I-ORG I-NP I-ORG B-NP O O
3-GRAM  3       I-ORG B-NP O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O B-PP O I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  1       O B-VP O I-ADVP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-NP O I-NP O I-CONJP
3-GRAM  5       O O I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O I-VP O O I-LOC I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-VP O O I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  2       B-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-PP O B-PP O I-VP
3-GRAM  2       O B-PP O I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-VP O I-NP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  2       O I-ADJP O O I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP O I-PP I-LOC O
3-GRAM  1       O I-PP I-LOC O O O
3-GRAM  2       O I-PP O I-PP O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O I-SBAR O I-NP O I-CONJP
3-GRAM  1       O I-CONJP O I-CONJP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  1       O I-CONJP O I-ADJP O O
3-GRAM  2       O O I-ORG O O I-VP
3-GRAM  2       I-ORG O O I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  7       I-MISC I-PP I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-NP I-MISC B-NP O O
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC B-NP O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O I-ADVP O B-ADVP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       O B-ADVP O I-ADVP O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP O I-NP I-PER I-PP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-PP I-PER I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC B-NP I-MISC I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  3       O O I-MISC I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP O I-PP I-ORG I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PP I-ORG I-PP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O O O I-SBAR O O
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP O I-NP I-LOC O
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-LOC O O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC O O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-NP I-PER I-ADVP O I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O I-NP I-PER I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-ADJP O I-PP O O
3-GRAM  1       O O I-PER I-ADVP O O
3-GRAM  4       O O O I-VP I-PER I-VP
3-GRAM  2       O I-VP I-PER I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  3       I-PER I-VP O I-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O B-PP I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-ADVP I-MISC I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP O I-NP I-PER I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP O I-LST O O
3-GRAM  1       O I-LST O O O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       O O O I-NP I-ORG I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-NP B-MISC I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       B-MISC I-NP O I-PP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O B-NP O I-SBAR O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP O O I-PER I-ADJP
3-GRAM  1       O O I-PER I-ADJP O O
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-ADJP O O I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  4       O I-VP O I-PRT I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-PRT I-LOC I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-NP O I-ADJP O I-VP
3-GRAM  8       I-LOC I-NP I-MISC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  1       O I-SBAR O I-VP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  2       O I-VP O I-PRT O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  2       O I-PRT O I-ADJP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-NP O I-VP I-ORG I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O I-VP I-ORG I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-NP O I-NP I-ORG O
3-GRAM  2       O I-NP I-ORG O O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP O I-INTJ I-LOC I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O I-INTJ I-LOC I-VP I-LOC I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-VP I-LOC I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-VP O I-PP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  7       O O I-ORG I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  4       O I-PP I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-PP
3-GRAM  5       O I-NP I-PER I-NP I-PER O
3-GRAM  3       I-PER I-NP I-PER O O O
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP O I-PP I-ORG I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PP I-ORG I-VP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O I-ADVP O B-ADVP O O
3-GRAM  1       O B-ADVP O O I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-NP I-ORG I-SBAR I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-SBAR I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-SBAR I-ORG I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-NP I-ORG B-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-ORG B-NP O B-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-PP O I-PP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O B-PP I-LOC I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  4       I-MISC I-NP O B-NP O O
3-GRAM  1       O B-ADVP O I-ADVP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O O I-PER I-NP I-PER I-PP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-NP I-PER I-PP O O
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-PP O O I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O O I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-ADVP O O
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG O O I-VP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O B-PP I-ORG I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-VP I-PER I-VP O B-VP
3-GRAM  2       I-PER I-VP O B-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP O I-NP I-ORG I-INTJ
3-GRAM  1       O B-NP O O I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PP O O O I-CONJP
3-GRAM  1       O O O I-CONJP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O O I-MISC I-NP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-NP O I-ADJP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-LOC I-ADVP O I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  2       I-MISC I-VP O I-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O B-VP O I-VP O B-VP
3-GRAM  2       O B-VP O I-VP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  4       I-PER B-NP O O I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-VP O I-SBAR O O
3-GRAM  2       I-ORG O O O O O
3-GRAM  1       O O I-LOC I-NP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP O I-ADJP O I-VP
3-GRAM  2       O O I-ORG I-INTJ I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-INTJ I-ORG I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O O O I-PP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  3       O I-SBAR I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADVP O O I-ORG I-INTJ
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-INTJ I-ORG I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  2       O I-NP I-ORG I-INTJ I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-ORG I-INTJ I-ORG I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PRT O I-SBAR O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-PER O O I-VP
3-GRAM  2       I-PER O O I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O O I-PER O O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-MISC I-NP O I-ADVP O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP O B-NP O I-PRT
3-GRAM  1       O B-NP O I-PRT O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-LOC I-NP B-LOC I-PP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP B-LOC I-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       B-LOC I-PP O I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  6       O I-NP I-LOC I-NP B-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  7       I-LOC I-NP B-LOC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  4       B-LOC I-NP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-LOC I-NP B-LOC O
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP B-LOC O O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       B-LOC O O I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  3       B-LOC I-NP O I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  4       O B-SBAR O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP I-LOC B-NP
3-GRAM  3       I-LOC I-NP I-LOC B-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC B-NP I-LOC I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  5       O O I-LOC I-NP I-LOC O
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-ORG O I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP I-LOC O I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-ADVP O I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-INTJ O O O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG B-NP O O O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O B-VP O I-ADJP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG B-NP O I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       B-MISC I-NP O I-NP I-ORG B-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-PER I-ADJP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-ADJP I-PER I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  3       I-LOC I-NP I-MISC I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PP I-LOC I-INTJ O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-INTJ O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O I-ADVP I-PER I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-NP I-ORG O I-ORG I-ADJP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG O I-ORG I-ADJP I-ORG O
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-ADJP I-ORG O I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADJP O I-VP O I-PRT
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-NP O I-PP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADJP O I-SBAR I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-LOC B-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC B-NP O I-ADVP O I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O B-PP I-LOC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-PP O O O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  1       B-MISC I-NP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-NP O I-PP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP O I-ADJP I-MISC I-ADJP
3-GRAM  2       O I-ADJP I-MISC I-ADJP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-ADJP O I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  2       O B-NP O I-PP O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-MISC B-NP O O
3-GRAM  6       I-ORG O I-ORG I-NP B-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  6       I-ORG I-NP B-ORG I-NP B-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  12      B-ORG I-NP B-ORG I-NP B-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  5       B-ORG I-NP B-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  5       B-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       B-ORG I-NP B-ORG I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       B-ORG I-NP O I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  3       I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP B-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  6       B-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  1       O B-PP I-LOC I-NP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-LOC I-VP O B-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-VP O B-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O I-ADJP O I-PP I-LOC I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PP I-LOC I-VP O O
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-VP O O O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-LOC I-VP O O
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP O I-PP I-LOC I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PP I-LOC I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-VP O I-PP O B-PP
3-GRAM  1       O I-SBAR O O O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O O O I-SBAR O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  4       O I-SBAR O I-ADVP O I-VP
3-GRAM  2       O B-NP O O O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  1       O I-PRT I-LOC I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-MISC I-NP O I-VP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  6       I-ORG I-NP O I-VP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  2       I-MISC I-NP O O I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O O O I-ADJP O I-SBAR
3-GRAM  2       O I-NP O I-NP I-LOC O
3-GRAM  2       O I-NP I-LOC O O O
3-GRAM  4       I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP I-PER B-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-VP I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-PP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER B-NP O O I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-MISC I-NP B-MISC I-NP I-MISC B-NP
3-GRAM  1       B-MISC I-NP I-MISC B-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  3       O I-ADJP O I-PP O I-ADJP
3-GRAM  2       O I-PP O I-ADJP O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-NP I-PER I-ADJP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-ADJP O I-PP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PP O I-NP B-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP B-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-SBAR O I-VP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP O I-NP I-PER O
3-GRAM  2       O I-NP I-PER O I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER O I-PER I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       O B-PP O I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O B-VP I-PER I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O B-PP I-MISC I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-INTJ I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-NP I-PER I-VP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-VP O I-PP O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-PER I-VP I-PER O
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-VP O O O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-VP O I-VP O O
3-GRAM  2       O I-VP O I-ADVP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O B-NP O I-ADVP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PP I-MISC I-VP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-MISC I-VP O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  1       O B-ADVP O I-ADVP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       O I-PP I-MISC I-NP B-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       B-MISC I-NP I-MISC B-NP O O
3-GRAM  3       I-ORG B-NP O I-NP O O
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP O I-PP I-MISC O
3-GRAM  1       O I-PP I-MISC O I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  2       I-MISC O I-MISC I-NP O O
3-GRAM  1       O B-NP I-MISC I-NP I-MISC O
3-GRAM  1       O I-SBAR O O I-PER O
3-GRAM  1       I-PER O I-PER O O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER O O I-NP O I-PP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-NP O O I-ORG I-ADJP
3-GRAM  1       O O I-ORG I-ADJP O O
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-ADJP O O O O
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG O O I-VP O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       O O I-LOC I-NP O I-CONJP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP O I-CONJP O I-CONJP
3-GRAM  1       O I-CONJP O I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-ADVP I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP O I-ADVP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP O I-INTJ
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-ADVP I-PER I-NP O I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       O O I-ORG I-NP I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-NP I-LOC I-NP O I-ADVP
3-GRAM  1       O I-VP I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-VP
3-GRAM  4       I-MISC I-VP I-MISC I-NP I-MISC I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG O I-ORG I-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-VP O I-NP I-ORG B-NP
3-GRAM  1       O I-NP I-ORG B-NP O B-NP
3-GRAM  2       O I-ADVP O O I-LOC I-NP
3-GRAM  7       I-ORG I-NP O I-PP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-ORG I-NP O I-PP O B-PP
3-GRAM  2       O B-PP I-ORG I-NP I-ORG I-NP
3-GRAM  4       I-PER I-NP I-PER O I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER O I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP
3-GRAM  1       I-PER I-NP I-PER I-NP I-PER O
3-GRAM  1       I-PER O I-PER I-NP O I-VP
3-GRAM  1       I-LOC B-NP I-LOC I-NP I-LOC I-PP
